[
    {
        "question": "1. What kind of book ______ your girlfriend buying?",
        "options": ["are", "has", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "2. Listen! The babies ______.",
        "options": ["are crying", "cry", "has crying"],
        "correctAnswer": "are crying"
    },
    {
        "question": "3. She ______ .",
        "options": ["is sometimes apologizing for her bad ways", "sometimes apologizes for her bad ways", "sometimes has apologizing for her bad ways"],
        "correctAnswer": "sometimes apologizes for her bad ways"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. My friends ______.",
        "options": ["are always feeling happy", "always feel happy", "are feeling happy always"],
        "correctAnswer": "always feel happy"
    },
    {
        "question": "5. Brian ______ your letter at the moment.",
        "options": ["reads", "has been reading", "is reading"],
        "correctAnswer": "is reading"
    },
    {
        "question": "6. The management team ______ this problem regularly.",
        "options": ["are discussing this problem regularly", "discuss this problem regularly", "have discuss this problem regularly"],
        "correctAnswer": "discuss this problem regularly"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. Usually, I ______ early.",
        "options": ["am getting up early", "have got up early", "get up early"],
        "correctAnswer": "get up early"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. Sarah ______ this castle.",
        "options": ["often visits this castle", "is often visiting this castle", "often visit this castle"],
        "correctAnswer": "often visits this castle"
    },
    {
        "question": "9. Look! The motorcycle ______ closer.",
        "options": ["gets closer", "is getting closer", "get closer"],
        "correctAnswer": "is getting closer"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. This awkward situation ______ quite regularly.",
        "options": ["is happening quite regularly", "have happened quite regularly", "happens quite regularly"],
        "correctAnswer": "happens quite regularly"
    },
    {
        "question": "11. Pay attention! The brick ______.",
        "options": ["falls", "is falling", "have fallen"],
        "correctAnswer": "is falling"
    },
    {
        "question": "12. They ______ to the gym three times a week.",
        "options": ["are going", "go", "have gone"],
        "correctAnswer": "go"
    },
    {
        "question": "13. She seldom ______ at the restaurant.",
        "options": ["appears", "appearing", "is appearing"],
        "correctAnswer": "appears"
    },
    {
        "question": "14. Choose the correct answer: He ______ complains.",
        "options": ["never complains", "is never complaining", "almost never complain"],
        "correctAnswer": "never complains"
    },
    {
        "question": "15. Choose the correct answer: They ______ each other several times a week.",
        "options": ["are calling one another several times a week", "have calling one another several times a week", "call each other several times a week"],
        "correctAnswer": "call each other several times a week"
    },
    {
        "question": "16. We ______ bad marks rarely.",
        "options": ["get", "have get", "are getting"],
        "correctAnswer": "get"
    },
    {
        "question": "17. The Browns ______ to help us very seldom.",
        "options": ["are refusing", "refuse", "refuses"],
        "correctAnswer": "refuse"
    },
    {
        "question": "18. Hey, Maria! Your boyfriend ______ for you.",
        "options": ["is still waiting", "still waits", "has still waiting"],
        "correctAnswer": "is still waiting"
    },
    {
        "question": "19. Choose the correct answer: Cris ______ her grandfather every two months.",
        "options": ["is visiting her grandfather every two months", "has visited her grandfather every two months", "visits her grandfather every two months"],
        "correctAnswer": "visits her grandfather every two months"
    },
    {
        "question": "20. I ______ very hard this weekend so as to finish the project.",
        "options": ["work", "worked", "am working"],
        "correctAnswer": "am working"
    },
    {
        "question": "21. It seems that Olivia ______ big problems this year.",
        "options": ["have", "experiences", "is experiencing"],
        "correctAnswer": "is experiencing"
    },
    {
        "question": "22. Choose the correct answer: I ______ with your opinion.",
        "options": ["utterly disagree with your opinion", "am totally disagreeing with you", "utterly have disagree with your opinion"],
        "correctAnswer": "utterly disagree with your opinion"
    },
    {
        "question": "23. Choose the correct answer: ______ my idea now?",
        "options": ["Do you like my idea now", "Are you liking my idea now", "Does you like my idea now"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do you like my idea now"
    },
    {
        "question": "24. Choose the correct answer: The conference ______ now.",
        "options": ["take place now", "is taking place now", "takes place now"],
        "correctAnswer": "is taking place now"
    },
    {
        "question": "25. Choose the correct answer: This song ______ strange now.",
        "options": ["isn't sounding strange now", "don't sound strange now", "doesn't sound strange now"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't sound strange now"
    },
    {
        "question": "26. Choose the correct answer: I ______ him now.",
        "options": ["really hate", "am really hating", "really hating"],
        "correctAnswer": "really hate"
    },
    {
        "question": "27. Choose the correct answer: Sarah ______ about it now.",
        "options": ["talks about it now", "is talking about it now", "talking about it now"],
        "correctAnswer": "is talking about it now"
    },
    {
        "question": "28. Choose the correct answer: I ______ with you now.",
        "options": ["don't agree with you now", "am not agreeing with you now", "not agree with you now"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't agree with you now"
    },
    {
        "question": "29. Choose the correct answer: The professor ______ our papers now.",
        "options": ["corrects our papers now", "does correcting our papers now", "is correcting our papers now"],
        "correctAnswer": "is correcting our papers now"
    },
    {
        "question": "30. Choose the correct answer: All colleagues ______ at her now.",
        "options": ["are laughing at her now", "laugh at her now", "laughing her now"],
        "correctAnswer": "are laughing at her now"
    },
    {
        "question": "31. Choose the correct answer: I ______ you well now.",
        "options": ["am understanding you well now", "do understand you well now", "have understanding you now"],
        "correctAnswer": "do understand you well now"
    },
    {
        "question": "32. Choose the correct answer: They ______ Brian actively now.",
        "options": ["support Brian actively now", "are supporting Brian actively now", "supporting Brian actively now"],
        "correctAnswer": "are supporting Brian actively now"
    },
    {
        "question": "33. Choose the correct answer: Our revolutionary project ______ of three parts now.",
        "options": ["consists of three parts now", "is consisting of three parts now", "consisting of three parts now"],
        "correctAnswer": "consists of three parts now"
    },
    {
        "question": "34. Choose the correct answer: The business ______ to her now.",
        "options": ["is belonging to her now", "has belonging to her now", "belongs to her now"],
        "correctAnswer": "belongs to her now"
    },
    {
        "question": "35. Choose the correct answer: I ______ the cake now.",
        "options": ["am really wanting the cake now", "really wanting the cake now", "really want the cake now"],
        "correctAnswer": "really want the cake now"
    },
    {
        "question": "36. Choose the correct answer: I ______ you fairly well now.",
        "options": ["hear you fairly well now", "am hearing you fairly well now", "hearing you fairly well now"],
        "correctAnswer": "hear you fairly well now"
    },
    {
        "question": "37. Choose the correct answer: Hey! Calm down! I ______ you now.",
        "options": ["am believing you now", "believe you now", "do believing you now"],
        "correctAnswer": "believe you now"
    },
    {
        "question": "38. Choose the correct answer: She ______ to understand the problem only now.",
        "options": ["tries to understand the problem only now", "is trying to understand the problem only now", "does trying to understand the problem only now"],
        "correctAnswer": "is trying to understand the problem only now"
    },
    {
        "question": "39. Choose the correct answer: They ______ to discuss the matter right now.",
        "options": ["need to discuss the matter right now", "are needing to discuss the matter right now", "are needing discussing the matter right now"],
        "correctAnswer": "need to discuss the matter right now"
    },
    {
        "question": "40. Choose the correct answer: The firm ______ the situation now.",
        "options": ["controls the situation now", "is controlling the situation now", "do controlling the situation now"],
        "correctAnswer": "controls the situation now"
    },
    {
        "question": "41. Choose the correct answer: John ______ gifts now.",
        "options": ["receives gifts now", "is receiving gifts now", "do receiving gifts now"],
        "correctAnswer": "is receiving gifts now"
    },
    {
        "question": "42. Choose the correct answer: They ______ to change their security strategy now.",
        "options": ["are beginning to change their security strategy now", "begin to change their security strategy now", "do beginning to change their security strategy now"],
        "correctAnswer": "are beginning to change their security strategy now"
    },
    {
        "question": "43. Choose the correct answer: I ______ a business meeting with them now.",
        "options": ["arrange a business meeting with them now", "arranging a business meeting with them now", "am arranging a business meeting with them now"],
        "correctAnswer": "am arranging a business meeting with them now"
    },
    {
        "question": "44. Choose the correct answer: I ______ this is the most effective method of learning Spanish.",
        "options": ["are supposing", "suppose", "do supposing"],
        "correctAnswer": "suppose"
    },
    {
        "question": "45. Choose the correct answer: He ______ this gorgeous car now.",
        "options": ["is owning this gorgeous car now", "owns this gorgeous car now", "does own this gorgeous car now"],
        "correctAnswer": "owns this gorgeous car now"
    },
    {
        "question": "46. Choose the correct answer: The box ______ five toys now.",
        "options": ["contains five toys now", "is containing five toys now", "does contains five toys now"],
        "correctAnswer": "contains five toys now"
    },
    {
        "question": "47. Choose the correct answer: She ______ her mistake now.",
        "options": ["repeats her mistake now", "is repeating her mistake now", "does repeating her mistake now"],
        "correctAnswer": "is repeating her mistake now"
    },
    {
        "question": "48. Choose the correct answer: Bill ______ her recommendations now.",
        "options": ["follows her recommendations now", "do follow her recommendations now", "is following her recommendations now"],
        "correctAnswer": "is following her recommendations now"
    },
    {
        "question": "49. Choose the correct answer: Now I ______ you good luck.",
        "options": ["wish you good luck", "am wishing you good luck", "do wishes you good luck"],
        "correctAnswer": "wish you good luck"
    },
    {
        "question": "50. Choose the correct answer: Success ______ only on you now.",
        "options": ["depends only on you now", "is depending only on you now", "do depending only on you now"],
        "correctAnswer": "depends only on you now"
    },
    {
        "question": "51. Choose the correct answer: ______ you meaning now?",
        "options": ["What are you meaning now", "What do you mean now", "What does you meaning now"],
        "correctAnswer": "What do you mean now"
    },
    {
        "question": "52. Choose the correct answer: We ______ Spanish now.",
        "options": ["practice", "have practiced", "are practicing"],
        "correctAnswer": "are practicing"
    },
    {
        "question": "53. Choose the correct answer: The employees ______ their products now.",
        "options": ["are promoting their products now", "promote their products now", "employees have promoting their products now"],
        "correctAnswer": "are promoting their products now"
    },
    {
        "question": "54. Choose the correct answer: I'm sorry. I ______ to take my words back now.",
        "options": ["am preferring to take my words back now", "prefer to take back my words now", "have preferred to take back my words now"],
        "correctAnswer": "prefer to take back my words now"
    },
    {
        "question": "55. Choose the correct answer: She ______ it very well now.",
        "options": ["is knowing it very well now", "knows it very well now", "will know it very well now"],
        "correctAnswer": "knows it very well now"
    },
    {
        "question": "56. Choose the correct answer: Their father ______ now after that dreadful accident.",
        "options": ["is recovering now after that dreadful accident", "recovers now after dreadful accident", "does recovers now after that dreadful accident"],
        "correctAnswer": "is recovering now after that dreadful accident"
    },
    {
        "question": "57. Choose the correct answer: Their test result ______ incredible now.",
        "options": ["seems incredible now", "is seeming incredible now", "has seemed incredible now"],
        "correctAnswer": "seems incredible now"
    },
    {
        "question": "58. Choose the correct answer: I ______ this kind of food now.",
        "options": ["am disliking this kind of food now", "does dislike this kind of food now", "dislike this kind of food now"],
        "correctAnswer": "dislike this kind of food now"
    },
    {
        "question": "59. Choose the correct answer: Brian ______ it better than you now.",
        "options": ["is knowing it better than you now", "knows it better than you now", "has known it better than you now"],
        "correctAnswer": "knows it better than you now"
    },
    {
        "question": "60. Choose the correct answer: I perfectly ______ the situation now.",
        "options": ["realize the situation now", "am perfectly realizing the situation now", "have perfectly realized the situation now"],
        "correctAnswer": "realize the situation now"
    },
    {
        "question": "61. Choose the correct answer: This smartphone ______ over 1,000 dollars now.",
        "options": ["costs over 1,000 dollars now", "is costing over 1,000 dollars now", "has cost over 1,000 dollars now"],
        "correctAnswer": "costs over 1,000 dollars now"
    },
    {
        "question": "62. Choose the correct answer: We ______ about the final project now.",
        "options": ["think about the final project now", "are thinking about the final project now", "have thinking about the final project now"],
        "correctAnswer": "are thinking about the final project now"
    },
    {
        "question": "63. Choose the correct answer: The boys ______ a great time now.",
        "options": ["are having a great time now", "have a great time now", "boys having a great time now"],
        "correctAnswer": "are having a great time now"
    },
    {
        "question": "64. Choose the correct answer: Olivia ______ a car now.",
        "options": ["is having a car now", "Olivia having a car now", "Olivia has a car now"],
        "correctAnswer": "Olivia has a car now"
    },
    {
        "question": "65. Choose the correct answer: I ______ about our future now.",
        "options": ["am thinking about our future now", "think about our future now", "have thinking about our future now"],
        "correctAnswer": "am thinking about our future now"
    },
    {
        "question": "66. Choose the correct answer: I completely ______ it's the right decision now.",
        "options": ["think it's the right decision now", "am completely thinking it's the right decision now", "thinking completely it's the right decision now"],
        "correctAnswer": "think it's the right decision now"
    },
    {
        "question": "67. Choose the correct answer: Thanks for asking! I ______ a good time now.",
        "options": ["have a good time now", "am having a good time now", "having a good time now"],
        "correctAnswer": "am having a good time now"
    },
    {
        "question": "68. Choose the correct answer: We ______ this project is a fiasco now.",
        "options": ["are thinking this project is a fiasco now", "thinking this project is a fiasco now", "think this project is a fiasco now"],
        "correctAnswer": "think this project is a fiasco now"
    },
    {
        "question": "69. Choose the correct answer: They ______ a party now.",
        "options": ["have a party now", "are having a party now", "having a party now"],
        "correctAnswer": "are having a party now"
    },
    {
        "question": "70. Choose the correct answer: I ______ three children now.",
        "options": ["have three children now", "am having three children now", "having three children now"],
        "correctAnswer": "have three children now"
    },
    {
        "question": "71. Choose the correct answer: I ______ two flats now.",
        "options": ["am having two flats now", "having two flats now", "have two flats now"],
        "correctAnswer": "have two flats now"
    },
    {
        "question": "72. This job is ........... difficult.",
        "options": ["such", "so", "such a"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "73. She is ........... clever.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "so a"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "74. These details are ........ important.",
        "options": ["such", "such as", "so"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "75. Your idea is ........... good.",
        "options": ["such", "so", "such a"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "76. What I heard is ....... a good idea.",
        "options": ["such", "so", "so and such"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "77. She is ........ a clever girl.",
        "options": ["so", "so and such", "such"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "78. Oh! It's ........... a difficult task!",
        "options": ["such", "so", "even"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "79. Hey! Look! This woman is ........... beautiful.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "even"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "80. You should pay attention. It's........... an important detail.",
        "options": ["so", "so and such", "such"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "81. Maria is.......... an alluring woman.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "even"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "82. The German lesson is ........... a useful one.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "by such"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "83. His success was ........ big.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "even"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "84. I consider that it was ........... a successful attempt.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "even"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "85. Your German lessons are ........... useful.",
        "options": ["such", "by so", "so"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "86. Have you noticed? This man is ........... strong.",
        "options": ["such", "by so", "so"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "87. Brian is ........... a strong man.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "by such"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "88. It's ..... a popular trend nowadays.",
        "options": ["such", "so", "by such"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "89. Wow! Thanks! It's ........... a brilliant idea.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "even"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "90. It was ........... a big victory.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "by so"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "91. This trend is. ........... popular nowadays.",
        "options": ["such", "by so", "so"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "92. He says ........... strange things.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "so a"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "93. The latest changes were ........... sudden.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "such a"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "94. Their questions were ...... curious.",
        "options": ["such", "so", "so a"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "95. All people were ........... friendly.",
        "options": ["such", "such a", "so"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "96. The Browns were ........... friendly people.",
        "options": ["so", "such as", "such"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "97. I have to admit. We were surprised by......... unpredictable results.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "such as"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "98. Sophia asked ........... curious questions.",
        "options": ["such", "such a", "so"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "99. We observed ........... sudden changes.",
        "options": ["so", "such", "such as"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "100. The professors were ........... strict there.",
        "options": ["such", "so", "so as"],
        "correctAnswer": "so"
    },
    {
        "question": "101. She has ........... a brilliant idea.",
        "options": ["so", "so as", "such"],
        "correctAnswer": "such"
    },
    {
        "question": "102. What would you like ..............?",
        "options": ["ordering", "order", "to order"],
        "correctAnswer": "to order"
    },
    {
        "question": "103. I would like ........... something identical.",
        "options": ["to experience", "experiencing", "experience"],
        "correctAnswer": "to experience"
    },
    {
        "question": "104. She would like ........... you an important thing.",
        "options": ["telling", "to tell", "tell"],
        "correctAnswer": "to tell"
    },
    {
        "question": "105. He would like .... his abilities.",
        "options": ["show", "showing", "to show"],
        "correctAnswer": "to show"
    },
    {
        "question": "106. I'm sorry........... I wouldn't like .",
        "options": ["overpay", "to overpay", "overpaying"],
        "correctAnswer": "to overpay"
    },
    {
        "question": "107. Would you like ........... it one more time?",
        "options": ["to do", "do", "doing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "108. They would like ........... you for everything that you've done.",
        "options": ["thank", "to thank", "thanking"],
        "correctAnswer": "to thank"
    },
    {
        "question": "109. Brian would like ........... Spanish as soon as possible.",
        "options": ["learning", "to learn", "learn"],
        "correctAnswer": "to learn"
    },
    {
        "question": "110. I would like ........... English.",
        "options": ["teaching", "teach", "to teach"],
        "correctAnswer": "to teach"
    },
    {
        "question": "111. He wouldn't like ......... his own website.",
        "options": ["having", "have", "to have"],
        "correctAnswer": "to have"
    },
    {
        "question": "112. I don't want ........... my patience.",
        "options": ["lose", "losing", "to lose"],
        "correctAnswer": "to lose"
    },
    {
        "question": "113. Please, let's go! Do you want ........... it right now?",
        "options": ["to finish", "finish", "finishing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to finish"
    },
    {
        "question": "114. Her student wants ........... more natural.",
        "options": ["sound", "to sound", "sounding"],
        "correctAnswer": "to sound"
    },
    {
        "question": "115. Do you really want ........... your progress immediately?",
        "options": ["seeing", "see", "to see"],
        "correctAnswer": "to see"
    },
    {
        "question": "116. Olivia wants ........... everything.",
        "options": ["to explain", "explain", "explaining"],
        "correctAnswer": "to explain"
    },
    {
        "question": "117. As far as I know, they don't want ........... new products.",
        "options": ["produce", "to produce", "producing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to produce"
    },
    {
        "question": "118. Cristina wants ........... this problem urgently.",
        "options": ["solve", "solving", "to solve"],
        "correctAnswer": "to solve"
    },
    {
        "question": "119. They want ........... their pronunciation.",
        "options": ["improve", "to improve", "improving"],
        "correctAnswer": "to improve"
    },
    {
        "question": "120. Well, I don't agree with that. I want ........... much less money.",
        "options": ["paying", "pay", "to pay"],
        "correctAnswer": "to pay"
    },
    {
        "question": "121. He wants ........... to native speakers more.",
        "options": ["to listen", "listen", "listening"],
        "correctAnswer": "to listen"
    },
    {
        "question": "122. They ........... to double their profit.",
        "options": ["won't", "want", "are wanting"],
        "correctAnswer": "want"
    },
    {
        "question": "123. I'm sorry. We............. guarantee anything.",
        "options": ["won't", "want", "are wanting"],
        "correctAnswer": "won't"
    },
    {
        "question": "124. Brian ........... to try to do it one more time.",
        "options": ["is wanting", "won't", "wants"],
        "correctAnswer": "wants"
    },
    {
        "question": "125. No matter what, I ........... argue with them.",
        "options": ["want", "won't", "am wanting"],
        "correctAnswer": "won't"
    },
    {
        "question": "126. They ........... to focus on the main problem.",
        "options": ["won't", "want", "are wanting"],
        "correctAnswer": "want"
    },
    {
        "question": "127. She ........... feel comfortable in this situation.",
        "options": ["won't", "want", "is wanting"],
        "correctAnswer": "won't"
    },
    {
        "question": "128. As far as I know, they ........... to improve their pronunciation.",
        "options": ["are wanting", "won't", "want"],
        "correctAnswer": "want"
    },
    {
        "question": "129. We ........... to congratulate you on this special occasion.",
        "options": ["won't", "want", "are wanting"],
        "correctAnswer": "want"
    },
    {
        "question": "130. I believe it ........... frighten them.",
        "options": ["won't", "want", "isn't wanting"],
        "correctAnswer": "won't"
    },
    {
        "question": "131. She ........... disagree with us on this matter.",
        "options": ["want", "is wanting", "won't"],
        "correctAnswer": "won't"
    },
    {
        "question": "132. He likes ...........",
        "options": ["to swim", "swim", "swimming"],
        "correctAnswer": "to swim"
    },
    {
        "question": "133. I like ........... Spanish.",
        "options": ["speaking", "to speak", "speak"],
        "correctAnswer": "speaking"
    },
    {
        "question": "134. He likes ........... other people how to do it.",
        "options": ["teach", "teaching", "to teach"],
        "correctAnswer": "to teach"
    },
    {
        "question": "135. My grandfather likes ............. fruit and vegetables in his own garden.",
        "options": ["grow", "to growing", "growing"],
        "correctAnswer": "growing"
    },
    {
        "question": "136. They like ............ strange things now.",
        "options": ["do", "to doing", "to do"],
        "correctAnswer": "to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "137. I like ........... Russian.",
        "options": ["learn", "learning", "to learning"],
        "correctAnswer": "learning"
    },
    {
        "question": "138. She likes.......... exotic languages.",
        "options": ["to learn", "learning", "to learning"],
        "correctAnswer": "learning"
    },
    {
        "question": "139. I know that you like ........... out.",
        "options": ["to eating", "eat", "eating"],
        "correctAnswer": "eating"
    },
    {
        "question": "140. We like ........... modern methods.",
        "options": ["to using", "use", "to use"],
        "correctAnswer": "to use"
    },
    {
        "question": "141. She likes ........... to classical music, which is surprising.",
        "options": ["listening", "to listen", "listen"],
        "correctAnswer": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question": "142. He doesn't like ........... formal clothes.",
        "options": ["wearing", "wear", "to wear"],
        "correctAnswer": "wearing"
    },
    {
        "question": "143. Laura doesn't like ........... at home all day.",
        "options": ["cook", "to cooking", "cooking"],
        "correctAnswer": "cooking"
    },
    {
        "question": "144. I don't like ........... my time.",
        "options": ["waste", "wasting", "to wasting"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasting"
    },
    {
        "question": "145. They don't like ........... this kind of things.",
        "options": ["discuss", "to discuss", "to discussing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to discuss"
    },
    {
        "question": "146. It's obvious. They don't like ........... it.",
        "options": ["to do", "do", "doing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to do"
    },
    {
        "question": "147. I've changed. Now, I don't like ........... TV.",
        "options": ["watching", "watch", "to watch"],
        "correctAnswer": "watching"
    },
    {
        "question": "148. She doesn't like ........... jogging.",
        "options": ["go", "to going", "going"],
        "correctAnswer": "going"
    },
    {
        "question": "149. We don't like ........... this subject anymore.",
        "options": ["mention", "to mention", "to mentioning"],
        "correctAnswer": "to mention"
    },
    {
        "question": "150. I see that you don't like ...........",
        "options": ["to lying", "lying", "to lie"],
        "correctAnswer": "to lie"
    },
    {
        "question": "151. She doesn't like ........... other people.",
        "options": ["to criticize", "criticize", "criticizing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to criticize"
    },
    {
        "question": "152. Does she like ........... chess?",
        "options": ["play", "to play", "playing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to play"
    },
    {
        "question": "153. Do you like ........... my car?",
        "options": ["driving", "drive", "to drive"],
        "correctAnswer": "to drive"
    },
    {
        "question": "154. Do you like ........... music?",
        "options": ["listen", "to listen", "to hear"],
        "correctAnswer": "to listen"
    },
    {
        "question": "155. Does she like ........... him questions?",
        "options": ["to put", "ask", "to ask"],
        "correctAnswer": "to ask"
    },
    {
        "question": "156. Do they like .......... about politics?",
        "options": ["talk", "talking", "to talking"],
        "correctAnswer": "talking"
    },
    {
        "question": "157. Do you like ........... exams?",
        "options": ["take", "to take", "to taking"],
        "correctAnswer": "to take"
    },
    {
        "question": "158. Do you like ....... orders to others?",
        "options": ["to give", "to giving", "giving"],
        "correctAnswer": "to give"
    },
    {
        "question": "159. Honestly speaking, do you like ........... football?",
        "options": ["to play", "play", "to playing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to play"
    },
    {
        "question": "160. Does she like ... to school?",
        "options": ["go", "to going", "to go"],
        "correctAnswer": "to go"
    },
    {
        "question": "161. Does he like .... his lessons?",
        "options": ["recording", "record", "to record"],
        "correctAnswer": "to record"
    },
    {
        "question": "162. Could you show me ........ thing?",
        "options": ["those", "these", "this"],
        "correctAnswer": "this"
    },
    {
        "question": "163. Tell us all ........... things.",
        "options": ["this", "these", "that"],
        "correctAnswer": "these"
    },
    {
        "question": "164. ........... decision is surprising for us.",
        "options": ["These", "Those", "This"],
        "correctAnswer": "This"
    },
    {
        "question": "165. In the end, she chose.......... thing.",
        "options": ["that", "these", "those"],
        "correctAnswer": "that"
    },
    {
        "question": "166. ........... words motivated me a lot to do it.",
        "options": ["This", "Those", "That"],
        "correctAnswer": "Those"
    },
    {
        "question": "167. She told me ........... bad news.",
        "options": ["these", "those", "this"],
        "correctAnswer": "this"
    },
    {
        "question": "168. They received ........... presents.",
        "options": ["that", "this", "those"],
        "correctAnswer": "those"
    },
    {
        "question": "169. ........... money belongs to her.",
        "options": ["This", "These", "Those"],
        "correctAnswer": "This"
    },
    {
        "question": "170. ........... shoes look so interesting.",
        "options": ["This", "These", "That"],
        "correctAnswer": "These"
    },
    {
        "question": "171. ........... knowledge is absolutely more than enough.",
        "options": ["These", "Those", "This"],
        "correctAnswer": "This"
    },
    {
        "question": "172. He ........... a good memory.",
        "options": ["having", "has", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "173. Maria ........... a boyfriend.",
        "options": ["has", "have", "having"],
        "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "174. Briana ........... a son.",
        "options": ["have", "have got", "has got"],
        "correctAnswer": "has got"
    },
    {
        "question": "175. They ........... a day off.",
        "options": ["has", "have", "has got"],
        "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
        "question": "176. We ........... such unpredictable result.",
        "options": ["has got", "has", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
        "question": "177. I ........... a motorcycle.",
        "options": ["has", "having", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
        "question": "178. She ........ a unique opportunity.",
        "options": ["has got", "have", "have got"],
        "correctAnswer": "has got"
    },
    {
        "question": "179. She ........... an interesting idea.",
        "options": ["have", "having", "has got"],
        "correctAnswer": "has got"
    },
    {
        "question": "180. John ............. three daughters.",
        "options": ["have", "has", "have got"],
        "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "181. It ........... many serious disadvantages. I don't buy it.",
        "options": ["have", "having", "has got"],
        "correctAnswer": "has got"
    },
    {
        "question": "182. Her husband ........... a bad mood.",
        "options": ["have", "has", "have got"],
        "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "183. Be careful! These people ........... many influential friends.",
        "options": ["has", "having", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "have"
    },
    {
        "question": "184. The following problem ........... another side to be discussed.",
        "options": ["has", "have", "having"],
        "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "185. The stories ........... a strange end.",
        "options": ["has got", "has", "have got"],
        "correctAnswer": "have got"
    },
    {
        "question": "186. Its economy ........... lots of weaknesses.",
        "options": ["have", "having", "has got"],
        "correctAnswer": "has got"
    },
    {
        "question": "187. We should use it. Their method ........... many advantages.",
        "options": ["have", "has", "have got"],
        "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "188. This tool ........... many disadvantages.",
        "options": ["have", "has", "having"],
        "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "189. This movement ........... so many followers.",
        "options": ["have", "have got", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "190. My friend ........... a new motorcycle.",
        "options": ["have got", "have", "has got"],
        "correctAnswer": "has got"
    },
    {
        "question": "191. The company ........... big financial problems.",
        "options": ["has", "have", "having"],
        "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "192. He ........... any ideas.",
        "options": ["haven't got", "hasn't get", "hasn't got"],
        "correctAnswer": "hasn't got"
    },
    {
        "question": "193. This bicycle ........... an owner.",
        "options": ["don't has", "don't have", "doesn't have"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't have"
    },
    {
        "question": "194. They ........... many fans.",
        "options": ["don't have", "doesn't have", "don't has"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't have"
    },
    {
        "question": "195. He ........... children.",
        "options": ["haven't got", "hasn't got", "hasn't get"],
        "correctAnswer": "hasn't got"
    },
    {
        "question": "196. You ........... your personal point of view, which is strange.",
        "options": ["hasn't got", "hasn't get", "haven't got"],
        "correctAnswer": "haven't got"
    },
    {
        "question": "197. They ........... an enormous office.",
        "options": ["don't has", "hasn't got", "haven't got"],
        "correctAnswer": "haven't got"
    },
    {
        "question": "198. You know that I ........... got an alternative.",
        "options": ["haven't", "hasn't", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "haven't"
    },
    {
        "question": "199. She ............. funny videos.",
        "options": ["don't have", "haven't got", "doesn't have"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't have"
    },
    {
        "question": "200. It ........... any growth.",
        "options": ["don't have", "don't has", "hasn't got"],
        "correctAnswer": "hasn't got"
    },
    {
        "question": "201. We ............ such a great teacher.",
        "options": ["hasn't got", "haven't got", "doesn't have"],
        "correctAnswer": "haven't got"
    },
    {
        "question": "202. Most people usually ............. have a clear-defined strategy.",
        "options": ["don't", "doesn't", "didn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "203. The university ........... have all the necessary equipment.",
        "options": ["don't", "doesn't", "hasn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "204. The professor ........... got any experience at all.",
        "options": ["have", "hasn't", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "hasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "205. Her business ........... have a good prospects.",
        "options": ["don't", "hasn't", "doesn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "206. Our friend .... got much money.",
        "options": ["haven't", "hasn't", "don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "hasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "207. To my surprise, the players ........... have a feeling of disappointment.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "208. The organization ........... have many members.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "209. My wife...........got a job, currently.",
        "options": ["didn't", "haven't", "hasn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "hasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "210. As far as I know, John's car ........... have a powerful engine.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "211. This business manager ........... got a good income.",
        "options": ["don't", "hasn't", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "hasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "212. ........... you have this kind of information?",
        "options": ["Does", "Have", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "213. ........... he got a constant income?",
        "options": ["Have", "Has", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Has"
    },
    {
        "question": "214. .......she have so many problems?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "215. ..........he got a girlfriend?",
        "options": ["Do", "Has", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Has"
    },
    {
        "question": "216. ........... you got a husband?",
        "options": ["Does", "Have", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Have"
    },
    {
        "question": "217. ........... he got some more successful projects?",
        "options": ["Have", "Do", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Has"
    },
    {
        "question": "218. ........... you have many children?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "219. ........... you have any questions for me?",
        "options": ["Does", "Have", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "220. ........... she have poor speaking skills?",
        "options": ["Does", "Have", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "221. ........... he have enough knowledge of this matter?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "222. ........... this approach have many advantages?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "223. ........... your husband got a motorcycle?",
        "options": ["Do", "Have", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Has"
    },
    {
        "question": "224. ........... this person have many connections?",
        "options": ["Have", "Do", "Does"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "225. ........... your cousin got a girlfriend?",
        "options": ["Do", "Has", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Has"
    },
    {
        "question": "226. ........... most people have this weird ideas?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "227. ........... your peers have some interesting ideas?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "228. ........... the college got a good reputation?",
        "options": ["Have", "Has", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Has"
    },
    {
        "question": "229. ........... the university got outstanding players?",
        "options": ["Have", "Has", "Does"],
        "correctAnswer": "Has"
    },
    {
        "question": "230. ........... this blog got short videos?",
        "options": ["Have", "Do", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Has"
    },
    {
        "question": "231. ........... this food have many healthy ingredients?",
        "options": ["Does", "Have", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "232. We can ........... Spanish quite fast if we use the right method.",
        "options": ["to learn", "learn", "learning"],
        "correctAnswer": "learn"
    },
    {
        "question": "233. Please, think about it. This project can........... you more money than you think.",
        "options": ["bring", "to bring", "bringing"],
        "correctAnswer": "bring"
    },
    {
        "question": "234. Leave it for now. She can ........... it later.",
        "options": ["to decide", "deciding", "decide"],
        "correctAnswer": "decide"
    },
    {
        "question": "235. Don't panic. We can ........... this issue in three days' time.",
        "options": ["discuss", "to discuss", "discussing"],
        "correctAnswer": "discuss"
    },
    {
        "question": "236. She can ........... what you say but not right away.",
        "options": ["understand", "to understand", "understanding"],
        "correctAnswer": "understand"
    },
    {
        "question": "237. The company can ........... 4 million euros in this project.",
        "options": ["to invest", "invest", "investing"],
        "correctAnswer": "invest"
    },
    {
        "question": "238. It can ........... a huge success.",
        "options": ["to become", "become", "becoming"],
        "correctAnswer": "become"
    },
    {
        "question": "239. You can ........... your listening skills if you start listening to something in Russian much more.",
        "options": ["to improve", "improving", "improve"],
        "correctAnswer": "improve"
    },
    {
        "question": "240. You can ........... it down now.",
        "options": ["write", "to write", "writing"],
        "correctAnswer": "write"
    },
    {
        "question": "241. I can ........... it clearly now. Thanks!",
        "options": ["to see", "see", "seeing"],
        "correctAnswer": "see"
    },
    {
        "question": "242. We can't ........... this threat to our security.",
        "options": ["to prevent", "preventing", "prevent"],
        "correctAnswer": "prevent"
    },
    {
        "question": "243. I can't ........... this problem now.",
        "options": ["solve", "to solve", "solving"],
        "correctAnswer": "solve"
    },
    {
        "question": "244. I can't ........... Russian.",
        "options": ["speaking", "speak", "to speak"],
        "correctAnswer": "speak"
    },
    {
        "question": "245. I can't ........... on her. Maria can let me down.",
        "options": ["to rely", "relying", "rely"],
        "correctAnswer": "rely"
    },
    {
        "question": "246. John can't .... this problem. It's too big.",
        "options": ["to ignore", "ignore", "ignoring"],
        "correctAnswer": "ignore"
    },
    {
        "question": "247. I must admit. We can't ........... anything.",
        "options": ["to change", "change", "changing"],
        "correctAnswer": "change"
    },
    {
        "question": "248. He can't ........... what happened that night.",
        "options": ["to forget", "forget", "forgetting"],
        "correctAnswer": "forget"
    },
    {
        "question": "249. Cristina can't......... a new house.",
        "options": ["buy", "to buy", "buying"],
        "correctAnswer": "buy"
    },
    {
        "question": "250. I can't ........... these completely different aspects.",
        "options": ["comparing", "to compare", "compare"],
        "correctAnswer": "compare"
    },
    {
        "question": "251. She can't ........... to these new conditions.",
        "options": ["to adapt", "adapt", "adapting"],
        "correctAnswer": "adapt"
    },
    {
        "question": "252. Can he ........... a meeting for tomorrow?",
        "options": ["to arrange", "arrange", "arranging"],
        "correctAnswer": "arrange"
    },
    {
        "question": "253. Can you ........... the date of our private meeting?",
        "options": ["confirm", "to confirm", "confirming"],
        "correctAnswer": "confirm"
    },
    {
        "question": "254. Can they......... their knowledge with us?",
        "options": ["to share", "sharing", "share"],
        "correctAnswer": "share"
    },
    {
        "question": "255. Can you ........... it later?",
        "options": ["to discuss", "discuss", "discussing"],
        "correctAnswer": "discuss"
    },
    {
        "question": "256. Can we ........... with such a powerful company?",
        "options": ["compete", "to compete", "competing"],
        "correctAnswer": "compete"
    },
    {
        "question": "257. Can you ........... their meeting?",
        "options": ["to cancel", "cancel", "canceling"],
        "correctAnswer": "cancel"
    },
    {
        "question": "258. Can I ........... my Russian grammar by myself?",
        "options": ["to improve", "improving", "improve"],
        "correctAnswer": "improve"
    },
    {
        "question": "259. Can you ........... for the tests more thoroughly?",
        "options": ["to prepare", "prepare", "preparing"],
        "correctAnswer": "prepare"
    },
    {
        "question": "260. Can the mentor ........... our work one more time?",
        "options": ["to check", "check", "checking"],
        "correctAnswer": "check"
    },
    {
        "question": "261. Please, can you ........... me?",
        "options": ["to help", "helping", "help"],
        "correctAnswer": "help"
    },
    {
        "question": "262. You must ........... to the professor.",
        "options": ["to listen", "listen", "listening"],
        "correctAnswer": "listen"
    },
    {
        "question": "263. She must ........... his strategy.",
        "options": ["to change", "changing", "change"],
        "correctAnswer": "change"
    },
    {
        "question": "264. He must ........... his skills.",
        "options": ["develop", "to develop", "developing"],
        "correctAnswer": "develop"
    },
    {
        "question": "265. The girl must ........... the exam.",
        "options": ["to pass", "pass", "passing"],
        "correctAnswer": "pass"
    },
    {
        "question": "266. They must ........... our money.",
        "options": ["to return", "return", "returning"],
        "correctAnswer": "return"
    },
    {
        "question": "267. The company must ........... the car price.",
        "options": ["to reduce", "reduce", "reducing"],
        "correctAnswer": "reduce"
    },
    {
        "question": "268. If you want to succeed you must ........... these recommendations.",
        "options": ["follow", "to follow", "following"],
        "correctAnswer": "follow"
    },
    {
        "question": "269. He must ........... his speaking skills.",
        "options": ["to improve", "improving", "improve"],
        "correctAnswer": "improve"
    },
    {
        "question": "270. Now, we must ........... for their decision.",
        "options": ["to wait", "wait", "waiting"],
        "correctAnswer": "wait"
    },
    {
        "question": "271. I must ........... the first place in this contest.",
        "options": ["take", "to take", "taking"],
        "correctAnswer": "take"
    },
    {
        "question": "272. She mustn't ........... so foolishly.",
        "options": ["to act", "acting", "act"],
        "correctAnswer": "act"
    },
    {
        "question": "273. They mustn't ........... much money on the gift.",
        "options": ["to spend", "spend", "spending"],
        "correctAnswer": "spend"
    },
    {
        "question": "274. You mustn't ever ........... how much she helped you.",
        "options": ["to forget", "forget", "forgetting"],
        "correctAnswer": "forget"
    },
    {
        "question": "275. She knows she mustn't ........... about it.",
        "options": ["to worry", "worry", "worrying"],
        "correctAnswer": "worry"
    },
    {
        "question": "276. Whatever you decide, it mustn't ........... to a disaster.",
        "options": ["to lead", "leading", "lead"],
        "correctAnswer": "lead"
    },
    {
        "question": "277. You mustn't ........... this thing during the meeting.",
        "options": ["mention", "to mention", "mentioning"],
        "correctAnswer": "mention"
    },
    {
        "question": "278. You mustn't ........... too much or you'll feel bad.",
        "options": ["to eat", "eat", "eating"],
        "correctAnswer": "eat"
    },
    {
        "question": "279. You mustn't ........... the rules within our organization.",
        "options": ["break", "to break", "breaking"],
        "correctAnswer": "break"
    },
    {
        "question": "280. The company mustn't ........... the price during this month.",
        "options": ["to increase", "increase", "increasing"],
        "correctAnswer": "increase"
    },
    {
        "question": "281. You mustn't ........... you strategy this year.",
        "options": ["changing", "to change", "change"],
        "correctAnswer": "change"
    },
    {
        "question": "282. Must I ........... this task as soon as possible?",
        "options": ["to solve", "solve", "solving"],
        "correctAnswer": "solve"
    },
    {
        "question": "283. Must she ........... learning here?",
        "options": ["continue", "to continue", "continuing"],
        "correctAnswer": "continue"
    },
    {
        "question": "284. Must they ........... more money from us?",
        "options": ["to borrow", "borrow", "borrowing"],
        "correctAnswer": "borrow"
    },
    {
        "question": "285. Must I ........... better conditions for her?",
        "options": ["to provide", "provide", "providing"],
        "correctAnswer": "provide"
    },
    {
        "question": "286. Must I ........... it anyway or I have a choice?",
        "options": ["to do", "doing", "do"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "287. Must the organization ........... its operating costs?",
        "options": ["to reduce", "reduce", "reducing"],
        "correctAnswer": "reduce"
    },
    {
        "question": "288. Must we ........... everything?",
        "options": ["clean", "to clean", "cleaning"],
        "correctAnswer": "clean"
    },
    {
        "question": "289. Must he ........... that he is right or is obvious?",
        "options": ["to prove", "prove", "proving"],
        "correctAnswer": "prove"
    },
    {
        "question": "290. Must she ........... with everything?",
        "options": ["to agree", "to disagree", "agree"],
        "correctAnswer": "agree"
    },
    {
        "question": "291. Must he .............. this program?",
        "options": ["to install", "install", "installing"],
        "correctAnswer": "install"
    },
    {
        "question": "292. The team have ........... very hard.",
        "options": ["to work", "work", "working"],
        "correctAnswer": "to work"
    },
    {
        "question": "293. I'm sorry for her. She has ........... up very early.",
        "options": ["get", "to get", "getting"],
        "correctAnswer": "to get"
    },
    {
        "question": "294. I have ........... there on time. It's my dignity at stake.",
        "options": ["to be", "be", "being"],
        "correctAnswer": "to be"
    },
    {
        "question": "295. She has ........... a look at it.",
        "options": ["have", "to have", "having"],
        "correctAnswer": "to have"
    },
    {
        "question": "296. Adrian has ........... after them.",
        "options": ["look", "looking", "to look"],
        "correctAnswer": "to look"
    },
    {
        "question": "297. They have ........... something in their behavior.",
        "options": ["change", "to change", "changing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to change"
    },
    {
        "question": "298. You have ........ me.",
        "options": ["believe", "believing", "to believe"],
        "correctAnswer": "to believe"
    },
    {
        "question": "299. It's quite late. We have .........",
        "options": ["to go", "go", "going"],
        "correctAnswer": "to go"
    },
    {
        "question": "300. Hey! I have .......... you something.",
        "options": ["tell", "to tell", "telling"],
        "correctAnswer": "to tell"
    },
    {
        "question": "301. It's so late, I have ........... up.",
        "options": ["hurry", "hurrying", "to hurry"],
        "correctAnswer": "to hurry"
    },
    {
        "question": "302. You don't have ......... for such basic things.",
        "options": ["overpay", "to overpay", "overpaying"],
        "correctAnswer": "to overpay"
    },
    {
        "question": "303. I've understood you don't like it. It's ok. You don't have .......... part in that competition.",
        "options": ["taking", "take", "to take"],
        "correctAnswer": "to take"
    },
    {
        "question": "304. You don't have .... there. You can easily resign.",
        "options": ["to work", "work", "working"],
        "correctAnswer": "to work"
    },
    {
        "question": "305. She doesn't have ......... her promise.",
        "options": ["break", "broke", "to break"],
        "correctAnswer": "to break"
    },
    {
        "question": "306. I think I don't have ........... it. It's embarrassing.",
        "options": ["mention", "mentioning", "to mention"],
        "correctAnswer": "to mention"
    },
    {
        "question": "307. You don't have ...... it so seriously.",
        "options": ["take", "to take", "taking"],
        "correctAnswer": "to take"
    },
    {
        "question": "308. It's Sunday. I don't have .......... up so early.",
        "options": ["to get", "get", "getting"],
        "correctAnswer": "to get"
    },
    {
        "question": "309. If you don't want, you don't have ........... it.",
        "options": ["say", "said", "to say"],
        "correctAnswer": "to say"
    },
    {
        "question": "310. You don't have ......... all his recommendations. He might be wrong.",
        "options": ["follow", "following", "to follow"],
        "correctAnswer": "to follow"
    },
    {
        "question": "311. He doesn't have ........... her. She's provocative.",
        "options": ["answer", "to answer", "answered"],
        "correctAnswer": "to answer"
    },
    {
        "question": "312. Does she have ...... it in advance?",
        "options": ["know", "knew", "to know"],
        "correctAnswer": "to know"
    },
    {
        "question": "313. Do you have ........... it down or you memorize it?",
        "options": ["to write", "write", "writing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to write"
    },
    {
        "question": "314. I'm not comfortable. Does she have ........... everything?",
        "options": ["watch", "to watch", "watching"],
        "correctAnswer": "to watch"
    },
    {
        "question": "315. Do we have ........... it every day? It seems expensive.",
        "options": ["use", "to use", "using"],
        "correctAnswer": "to use"
    },
    {
        "question": "316. Do I have ........... the board all the time?",
        "options": ["inform", "informed", "to inform"],
        "correctAnswer": "to inform"
    },
    {
        "question": "317. She regrets it. Does she have ........... for it?",
        "options": ["apologize", "apologized", "to apologize"],
        "correctAnswer": "to apologize"
    },
    {
        "question": "318. Do I have ........... it daily? I really don't like this newspaper.",
        "options": ["to read", "read", "reading"],
        "correctAnswer": "to read"
    },
    {
        "question": "319. Do you have ........... a uniform? It's quite hot for that.",
        "options": ["wear", "wore", "to wear"],
        "correctAnswer": "to wear"
    },
    {
        "question": "320. Do you have .......... it in advance?",
        "options": ["plan", "to plan", "planning"],
        "correctAnswer": "to plan"
    },
    {
        "question": "321. Do they have ........... for his mistakes all the time?",
        "options": ["to pay", "pay", "paid"],
        "correctAnswer": "to pay"
    },
    {
        "question": "322. He thinks she should ........... weight.",
        "options": ["to lose", "lose", "losing"],
        "correctAnswer": "to lose"
    },
    {
        "question": "323. You should ........... more in English. Don't you think?",
        "options": ["to read", "reading", "read"],
        "correctAnswer": "to read"
    },
    {
        "question": "324. If you want the job, you should ........... your grammar.",
        "options": ["to improve", "improving", "improve"],
        "correctAnswer": "to improve"
    },
    {
        "question": "325. He should ........... on his mistakes and learn now things.",
        "options": ["to work", "work", "working"],
        "correctAnswer": "to work"
    },
    {
        "question": "326. You should ........... money more rationally. It's hard to make it.",
        "options": ["spend", "to spend", "spending"],
        "correctAnswer": "spend"
    },
    {
        "question": "327. You should ........... more. You look dead tired.",
        "options": ["to sleep", "sleep", "sleeping"],
        "correctAnswer": "sleep"
    },
    {
        "question": "328. I should ........... a spacious flat.",
        "options": ["to buy", "buying", "buy"],
        "correctAnswer": "buy"
    },
    {
        "question": "329. The kid should ........... sport more.",
        "options": ["to practice", "practice", "practicing"],
        "correctAnswer": "practice"
    },
    {
        "question": "330. You've damaged it. You should ........... more careful.",
        "options": ["be", "to be", "was"],
        "correctAnswer": "be"
    },
    {
        "question": "331. One should ........... after his health.",
        "options": ["to look", "looking", "look"],
        "correctAnswer": "look"
    },
    {
        "question": "332. She shouldn't ........... surprised. I've told her the news.",
        "options": ["being", "be", "to be"],
        "correctAnswer": "be"
    },
    {
        "question": "333. You shouldn't ...... ashamed of it. It happens.",
        "options": ["to be", "was", "be"],
        "correctAnswer": "be"
    },
    {
        "question": "334. They shouldn't ....... It's just a bee.",
        "options": ["panic", "to panic", "had panic"],
        "correctAnswer": "panic"
    },
    {
        "question": "335. The financial manager thinks that we shouldn't ........... the market but I don't think so.",
        "options": ["to monitor", "monitoring", "monitor"],
        "correctAnswer": "monitor"
    },
    {
        "question": "336. She shouldn't ........ all his mistakes. She's becoming annoying.",
        "options": ["corrected", "correct", "to correct"],
        "correctAnswer": "correct"
    },
    {
        "question": "337. You shouldn't ........ it.",
        "options": ["to guarantee", "guarantee", "guaranteed"],
        "correctAnswer": "guarantee"
    },
    {
        "question": "338. He shouldn't ........... such long breaks.",
        "options": ["make", "to make", "making"],
        "correctAnswer": "make"
    },
    {
        "question": "339. Oh, come on! You shouldn't ........... the government for everything that happens.",
        "options": ["to blame", "blamed", "blame"],
        "correctAnswer": "blame"
    },
    {
        "question": "340. I know I shouldn't ........... her mistakes but I need to try.",
        "options": ["to copy", "copy", "copying"],
        "correctAnswer": "copy"
    },
    {
        "question": "341. Daniel shouldn't ...... her anything.",
        "options": ["to promise", "promise", "promising"],
        "correctAnswer": "promise"
    },
    {
        "question": "342. Should she ....... at his mistakes?",
        "options": ["pointing", "to point", "point"],
        "correctAnswer": "point"
    },
    {
        "question": "343. Should they ........ critics and act differently?",
        "options": ["to forestall", "forestall", "forestalled"],
        "correctAnswer": "forestall"
    },
    {
        "question": "344. Should I ........... about moving together seriously?",
        "options": ["to think", "think", "thinking"],
        "correctAnswer": "think"
    },
    {
        "question": "345. Should he ........... his speech? It might be important.",
        "options": ["record", "to record", "recorded"],
        "correctAnswer": "record"
    },
    {
        "question": "346. Should they ........... only on this particular issue?",
        "options": ["focus", "focusing", "to focus"],
        "correctAnswer": "focus"
    },
    {
        "question": "347. Should we ........... on the main problem?",
        "options": ["concentrate", "concentrated", "to concentrate"],
        "correctAnswer": "concentrate"
    },
    {
        "question": "348. Should I ........... enough? it or is clear",
        "options": ["to repeat", "repeated", "repeat"],
        "correctAnswer": "repeat"
    },
    {
        "question": "349. Should we ........... in all gaps? I don't like this form.",
        "options": ["to fill", "fill", "filling"],
        "correctAnswer": "fill"
    },
    {
        "question": "350. Should we ........... our way of dealing with problems?",
        "options": ["revise", "to revise", "revising"],
        "correctAnswer": "revise"
    },
    {
        "question": "351. Should he ........... ready for it?",
        "options": ["to be", "be", "being"],
        "correctAnswer": "be"
    },
    {
        "question": "352. When she was rich, she ........ buy several apartments in the outskirts.",
        "options": ["can", "could", "can't"],
        "correctAnswer": "could"
    },
    {
        "question": "353. You could ........... me this thing right away.",
        "options": ["to tell", "tell", "told"],
        "correctAnswer": "tell"
    },
    {
        "question": "354. I remember that when he way young, he ........... run fast.",
        "options": ["can", "could", "can't"],
        "correctAnswer": "could"
    },
    {
        "question": "355. Is it ok? I could ........... it for you.",
        "options": ["repeat", "to repeat", "repeating"],
        "correctAnswer": "repeat"
    },
    {
        "question": "356. I could ........... you with great pleasure. Just ask.",
        "options": ["to help", "helping", "help"],
        "correctAnswer": "help"
    },
    {
        "question": "357. You could ........... a suitable candidate for this position.",
        "options": ["to find", "find", "finding"],
        "correctAnswer": "find"
    },
    {
        "question": "358. You could ........... up. We don't have all day.",
        "options": ["to hurry", "hurrying", "hurry"],
        "correctAnswer": "hurry"
    },
    {
        "question": "359. I ........... work much more five years ago.",
        "options": ["can", "can't", "could"],
        "correctAnswer": "could"
    },
    {
        "question": "360. I could ........... much better one year ago.",
        "options": ["to study", "study", "studied"],
        "correctAnswer": "study"
    },
    {
        "question": "361. Our professor could ........... it more clearly.",
        "options": ["explain", "to explain", "explaining"],
        "correctAnswer": "explain"
    },
    {
        "question": "362. The teacher couldn't ........... all his mistakes.",
        "options": ["to correct", "correct", "corrected"],
        "correctAnswer": "correct"
    },
    {
        "question": "363. Unfortunately, it couldn't ........... their losses.",
        "options": ["to cover", "cover", "covering"],
        "correctAnswer": "cover"
    },
    {
        "question": "364. This is amazing! She ........... run so fast two years ago.",
        "options": ["can't", "couldn't", "can"],
        "correctAnswer": "couldn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "365. I couldn't ........... it instead of her.",
        "options": ["do", "to do", "done"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "366. He........... buy such an expensive car last year.",
        "options": ["can't", "can", "couldn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "couldn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "367. I know it's rough but she couldn't ........... it another way.",
        "options": ["to do", "do", "done"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "368. John couldn't ........... now.",
        "options": ["to win", "won", "win"],
        "correctAnswer": "win"
    },
    {
        "question": "369. Much as I wanted, I couldn't ........... him more.",
        "options": ["pay", "paid", "to pay"],
        "correctAnswer": "pay"
    },
    {
        "question": "370. He tried but he couldn't ...... it.",
        "options": ["to hide", "hide", "hiding"],
        "correctAnswer": "hide"
    },
    {
        "question": "371. When he was a small boy, he ........... do it so well.",
        "options": ["can't", "can", "couldn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "couldn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "372. Could it ........... another place? I don't like that restaurant.",
        "options": ["to be", "be", "being"],
        "correctAnswer": "be"
    },
    {
        "question": "373. I haven't heard. Could you......... it again?",
        "options": ["say", "to say", "said"],
        "correctAnswer": "say"
    },
    {
        "question": "374. Could he ........... us some advice? We are in trouble.",
        "options": ["to give", "giving", "give"],
        "correctAnswer": "give"
    },
    {
        "question": "375. ........... they help her financially when she was a student?",
        "options": ["Can", "Can't", "Could"],
        "correctAnswer": "Could"
    },
    {
        "question": "376. Could he ........... just a little bit earlier?",
        "options": ["to come", "come", "came"],
        "correctAnswer": "come"
    },
    {
        "question": "377. Please, could you ........... it?",
        "options": ["repeat", "to repeat", "repeating"],
        "correctAnswer": "repeat"
    },
    {
        "question": "378. Could you ........... me, please? I need you.",
        "options": ["to help", "help", "helped"],
        "correctAnswer": "help"
    },
    {
        "question": "379. I'm busy. Could you ........... it down for me?",
        "options": ["to write", "write", "writing"],
        "correctAnswer": "write"
    },
    {
        "question": "380. Could you ........... Spanish? it? I don't know",
        "options": ["to translate", "translated", "translate"],
        "correctAnswer": "translate"
    },
    {
        "question": "381. ........... she dance so well when she was a schoolgirl?",
        "options": ["Can", "Can't", "Could"],
        "correctAnswer": "Could"
    },
    {
        "question": "382. You might ......... her for her ways.",
        "options": ["to criticize", "criticize", "criticizing"],
        "correctAnswer": "criticize"
    },
    {
        "question": "383. The team might ........... the final game.",
        "options": ["lose", "lost", "to lose"],
        "correctAnswer": "lose"
    },
    {
        "question": "384. It may ........... our difficult situation.",
        "options": ["to improve", "improved", "improve"],
        "correctAnswer": "improve"
    },
    {
        "question": "385. I may ........... my point of view.",
        "options": ["change", "changed", "to change"],
        "correctAnswer": "change"
    },
    {
        "question": "386. It might ........... our plans, which is not good.",
        "options": ["to destroy", "destroy", "destroyed"],
        "correctAnswer": "destroy"
    },
    {
        "question": "387. She might ........... with us. Be careful and express your arguments.",
        "options": ["to disagree", "disagree", "disagreed"],
        "correctAnswer": "disagree"
    },
    {
        "question": "388. It might ........... again. We should be careful.",
        "options": ["to happen", "happened", "happen"],
        "correctAnswer": "happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "389. They may ........... this text for practice.",
        "options": ["to translate", "translate", "translating"],
        "correctAnswer": "translate"
    },
    {
        "question": "390. The situation may ........... the same despite the army intervention.",
        "options": ["remain", "to remain", "remained"],
        "correctAnswer": "remain"
    },
    {
        "question": "391. This speech might ...... her.",
        "options": ["to motivate", "motivate", "motivated"],
        "correctAnswer": "motivate"
    },
    {
        "question": "392. She may not ........... her goal.",
        "options": ["to achieve", "achieve", "achieved"],
        "correctAnswer": "achieve"
    },
    {
        "question": "393. It might not ........... today.",
        "options": ["to rain", "rained", "rain"],
        "correctAnswer": "rain"
    },
    {
        "question": "394. The situation may not ........... greatly.",
        "options": ["improved", "improve", "to improve"],
        "correctAnswer": "improve"
    },
    {
        "question": "395. They might not ........... this problem.",
        "options": ["solve", "to solve", "solving"],
        "correctAnswer": "solve"
    },
    {
        "question": "396. It might not ....... this week.",
        "options": ["to snow", "snow", "will snow"],
        "correctAnswer": "snow"
    },
    {
        "question": "397. We might not ........... our plans regardless of your thoughts.",
        "options": ["to change", "changed", "change"],
        "correctAnswer": "change"
    },
    {
        "question": "398. I may not ........... this fitness club. I don't like the schedule.",
        "options": ["to join", "join", "joining"],
        "correctAnswer": "join"
    },
    {
        "question": "399. He may not ........... at the conference on women rights.",
        "options": ["to arrive", "arrive", "arriving"],
        "correctAnswer": "arrive"
    },
    {
        "question": "400. She might not ........... us correctly.",
        "options": ["understand", "understood", "to understand"],
        "correctAnswer": "understand"
    },
    {
        "question": "401. It might not ........... so sunny.",
        "options": ["to be", "be", "being"],
        "correctAnswer": "be"
    },
    {
        "question": "402. May it ........... a popular song?",
        "options": ["to become", "become", "becoming"],
        "correctAnswer": "become"
    },
    {
        "question": "403. May she ........... the police?",
        "options": ["to call", "called", "call"],
        "correctAnswer": "call"
    },
    {
        "question": "404. May Brian ........... everything by doing that?",
        "options": ["lost", "lose", "to lose"],
        "correctAnswer": "lose"
    },
    {
        "question": "405. Might this action ........... her life completely?",
        "options": ["change", "to change", "changed"],
        "correctAnswer": "change"
    },
    {
        "question": "406. Might he ........... soon after that dreadful accident?",
        "options": ["to recover", "recover", "recovered"],
        "correctAnswer": "recover"
    },
    {
        "question": "407. May she ........... very famous?",
        "options": ["to become", "become", "became"],
        "correctAnswer": "become"
    },
    {
        "question": "408. May he ........... it frankly?",
        "options": ["to say", "said", "say"],
        "correctAnswer": "say"
    },
    {
        "question": "409. Might it ........... our plans for the weekend?",
        "options": ["to spoil", "spoil", "spoilt"],
        "correctAnswer": "spoil"
    },
    {
        "question": "410. May he ........... this job?",
        "options": ["get", "to get", "got"],
        "correctAnswer": "get"
    },
    {
        "question": "411. May he ........... a mistake?",
        "options": ["to make", "make", "made"],
        "correctAnswer": "make"
    },
    {
        "question": "412. It ........... in Spain.",
        "options": ["produce", "is produced", "have produced"],
        "correctAnswer": "is produced"
    },
    {
        "question": "413. Briana and her friends..... by them",
        "options": ["criticize", "criticizing", "are criticized"],
        "correctAnswer": "are criticized"
    },
    {
        "question": "414. English ........... all over the world nowadays.",
        "options": ["speaks", "spoke", "is spoken"],
        "correctAnswer": "is spoken"
    },
    {
        "question": "415. It .... in China.",
        "options": ["is made", "makes", "are made"],
        "correctAnswer": "is made"
    },
    {
        "question": "416. The necessary conditions ........... there.",
        "options": ["provide", "are provided", "is provided"],
        "correctAnswer": "are provided"
    },
    {
        "question": "417. They ........... it in Britain.",
        "options": ["are made", "make", "is made"],
        "correctAnswer": "are made"
    },
    {
        "question": "418. It ........... in this document.",
        "options": ["wrote", "write", "is written"],
        "correctAnswer": "is written"
    },
    {
        "question": "419. Gas ........... there by Russians.",
        "options": ["supplies", "is supplied", "are supplied"],
        "correctAnswer": "is supplied"
    },
    {
        "question": "420. They ........... English.",
        "options": ["speak", "are spoken", "speaking"],
        "correctAnswer": "are spoken"
    },
    {
        "question": "421. Russians ........... gas.",
        "options": ["are supplied", "supply", "supplying"],
        "correctAnswer": "are supplied"
    },
    {
        "question": "422. This kind of news ...........",
        "options": ["are discussed", "is discussed", "are being discussed"],
        "correctAnswer": "is discussed"
    },
    {
        "question": "423. The goods ........... in India.",
        "options": ["is made", "are make", "are made"],
        "correctAnswer": "are made"
    },
    {
        "question": "424. During this training, our knowledge ........... to you.",
        "options": ["are given", "is gave", "is given"],
        "correctAnswer": "is given"
    },
    {
        "question": "425. The movement ....... by the young.",
        "options": ["is supported", "support", "are supported"],
        "correctAnswer": "is supported"
    },
    {
        "question": "426. Wow! This employee ........... a lot.",
        "options": ["are paid", "is pay", "is paid"],
        "correctAnswer": "is paid"
    },
    {
        "question": "427. As compared to others, these employees ........... less.",
        "options": ["is paid", "are paid", "paid"],
        "correctAnswer": "are paid"
    },
    {
        "question": "428. This castle ........... by many tourists every week.",
        "options": ["are visited", "is visited", "visits"],
        "correctAnswer": "is visited"
    },
    {
        "question": "429. This phone ........... in China.",
        "options": ["produced", "produces", "is produced"],
        "correctAnswer": "is produced"
    },
    {
        "question": "430. A lot of money ........... by us for their irreproachable services.",
        "options": ["are paid", "is paid", "pay"],
        "correctAnswer": "is paid"
    },
    {
        "question": "431. The letters ........... slowly.",
        "options": ["is written", "are written", "wrote"],
        "correctAnswer": "are written"
    },
    {
        "question": "432. My last boss ...........",
        "options": ["was respect", "respects", "was respected"],
        "correctAnswer": "was respected"
    },
    {
        "question": "433. After applying the strategy the costs ...........",
        "options": ["is reduced", "was reduced", "were reduced"],
        "correctAnswer": "were reduced"
    },
    {
        "question": "434. The sentence ........... You deserve a candy.",
        "options": ["are corrected", "were corrected", "was corrected"],
        "correctAnswer": "was corrected"
    },
    {
        "question": "435. I regret to announce that the information ...........",
        "options": ["were stolen", "was stolen", "are stolen"],
        "correctAnswer": "was stolen"
    },
    {
        "question": "436. Finally, the thieves ...........",
        "options": ["are cut", "is caught", "were caught"],
        "correctAnswer": "were caught"
    },
    {
        "question": "437. This subject ........... when I was at college.",
        "options": ["was taught", "were taught", "is taught"],
        "correctAnswer": "was taught"
    },
    {
        "question": "438. This sum of money ........... to him.",
        "options": ["were lent", "lent", "was lent"],
        "correctAnswer": "was lent"
    },
    {
        "question": "439. The news ........... much later.",
        "options": ["were heard", "was heard", "heard"],
        "correctAnswer": "was heard"
    },
    {
        "question": "440. Too little money ........... to help them.",
        "options": ["were received", "are received", "was received"],
        "correctAnswer": "was received"
    },
    {
        "question": "441. The last building ...........",
        "options": ["destroy", "have been destroyed", "was destroyed"],
        "correctAnswer": "was destroyed"
    },
    {
        "question": "442. The films ........... by them.",
        "options": ["don't produce", "isn't produced", "aren't produced"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't produced"
    },
    {
        "question": "443. This theory ........... very clearly.",
        "options": ["doesn't explain", "isn't explained", "hasn't explained"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't explained"
    },
    {
        "question": "444. These results ........... to what we know.",
        "options": ["don't compare", "are comparing", "aren't compared"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't compared"
    },
    {
        "question": "445. It ........... by her.",
        "options": ["doesn't decide", "isn't decided", "haven't decided"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't decided"
    },
    {
        "question": "446. The marketing manager ........... the situation.",
        "options": ["isn't liked", "don't like", "doesn't like"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't like"
    },
    {
        "question": "447. The books ........... this year.",
        "options": ["aren't published", "isn't published", "don't publish"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't published"
    },
    {
        "question": "448. This information ........... in the user guide.",
        "options": ["isn't mentioned", "aren't mentioned", "doesn't mention"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't mentioned"
    },
    {
        "question": "449. This method ........... by my colleagues.",
        "options": ["are used", "is used", "doesn't use"],
        "correctAnswer": "is used"
    },
    {
        "question": "450. As far as I know, they ........... these videos.",
        "options": ["aren't produce", "don't produce", "does produce"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't produce"
    },
    {
        "question": "451. This subject ........... at university.",
        "options": ["are taught", "doesn't taught", "isn't taught"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't taught"
    },
    {
        "question": "452. Her money ........... anywhere.",
        "options": ["isn't invested", "are invested", "is invest"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't invested"
    },
    {
        "question": "453. The important decisions in this company ........... by her.",
        "options": ["isn't taken", "aren't taken", "take"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't taken"
    },
    {
        "question": "454. His progress ............. although he works very hard.",
        "options": ["isn't seen", "sees", "aren't seen"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't seen"
    },
    {
        "question": "455. These details ........... in the manual.",
        "options": ["is described", "are described", "describe"],
        "correctAnswer": "are described"
    },
    {
        "question": "456. I know that this language ........... in many countries.",
        "options": ["aren't spoken", "speaks", "is spoken"],
        "correctAnswer": "is spoken"
    },
    {
        "question": "457. Such ideas ........... as wrong.",
        "options": ["isn't suggested", "aren't suggested", "suggest"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't suggested"
    },
    {
        "question": "458. The girl ........... to do it.",
        "options": ["isn't allowed", "allow", "aren't allowed"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't allowed"
    },
    {
        "question": "459. I'm sorry to inform you, but this service ...........",
        "options": ["isn't provided", "aren't provided", "provides"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't provided"
    },
    {
        "question": "460. It's obvious that although we have taken action, the costs ...........",
        "options": ["isn't reduced", "aren't reduced", "is reduced"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't reduced"
    },
    {
        "question": "461. These things ........... correctly by them.",
        "options": ["isn't understood", "aren't understood", "understand"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't understood"
    },
    {
        "question": "462. ........... correctly?",
        "options": ["Do this rule understand", "Is this rule understood", "Is this rule understand"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is this rule understood"
    },
    {
        "question": "463. Choose the correct answer: ______ these apartments sell?",
        "options": ["Do these apartments sell", "Are these apartments sold", "Are this apartments sold"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are these apartments sold"
    },
    {
        "question": "464. ........... on the blackboard?",
        "options": ["Is this text written", "Are these text written", "This text written is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is this text written"
    },
    {
        "question": "465. Choose the correct answer: ______ these titles included?",
        "options": ["Do these titles included", "Are these titles included", "Does these titles included"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are these titles included"
    },
    {
        "question": "466. ........... very important?",
        "options": ["Does this detail consider", "Is this detail considered", "Do this detail considers"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is this detail considered"
    },
    {
        "question": "467. ........... to do it?",
        "options": ["Does the boy allow", "Is the boy allow", "Is the boy allowed"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is the boy allowed"
    },
    {
        "question": "468. ........... in Paris?",
        "options": ["Is this language spoken", "Does this language spoken", "This language speaks"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is this language spoken"
    },
    {
        "question": "469. ........... to everyone who participates?",
        "options": ["Does it shows", "Is it shown", "Does it show"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is it shown"
    },
    {
        "question": "470. ........... it?",
        "options": ["Are the policemen check", "Do the policemen check", "The policemen check"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do the policemen check"
    },
    {
        "question": "471. Tell me more about this product ........... in France?",
        "options": ["Does it produces", "It produced", "Is it produced"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is it produced"
    },
    {
        "question": "472. Choose the correct answer: ______ all employees examined?",
        "options": ["Is all employees examined", "Are all employees examined", "Does all employees examined"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are all employees examined"
    },
    {
        "question": "473. Choose the correct answer: ______ her books published regularly?",
        "options": ["Are her books published regularly", "Is her books published regularly", "Does her books publish regularly"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are her books published regularly"
    },
    {
        "question": "474. Choose the correct answer: ______ the workers control?",
        "options": ["Are the workers control", "Is the workers controlled", "Are the workers controlled"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are the workers controlled"
    },
    {
        "question": "475. Choose the correct answer: ______ the students taught by an experienced teacher?",
        "options": ["Is the students taught by an experienced teacher", "Are the students teach by an experienced teacher", "Are the students taught by an experienced teacher"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are the students taught by an experienced teacher"
    },
    {
        "question": "476. Choose the correct answer: ______ the goods delivered?",
        "options": ["Is the goods delivered", "Are the goods delivered", "Do the goods delivered"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are the goods delivered"
    },
    {
        "question": "477. Choose the correct answer: ______ their achievements mentioned?",
        "options": ["Are their achievements mentioned", "Are their achievement mentioned", "Is their achievements mentioned"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are their achievements mentioned"
    },
    {
        "question": "478. Choose the correct answer: ______ these problems discussed there?",
        "options": ["Is these problems discussed there", "Are these problems discussed there", "Do these problems discussed there"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are these problems discussed there"
    },
    {
        "question": "479. Choose the correct answer: ______ the videos recorded?",
        "options": ["Is the videos recorded", "Are the videos recorded", "Do the videos recorded"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are the videos recorded"
    },
    {
        "question": "480. Choose the correct answer: ______ an organization uniform worn there?",
        "options": ["Are an organization uniform worn there", "Is an organization uniform worn there", "Does an organization uniform wear there"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is an organization uniform worn there"
    },
    {
        "question": "481. Choose the correct answer: ______ all the market conditions monitored?",
        "options": ["Are all the market conditions monitored", "Is all the market conditions monitored", "Does all the market conditions monitor"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are all the market conditions monitored"
    },
    {
        "question": "482. They ........... in a traffic jam.",
        "options": ["delayed", "delay", "were delayed"],
        "correctAnswer": "were delayed"
    },
    {
        "question": "483. He ........... in China",
        "options": ["bore", "was born", "born"],
        "correctAnswer": "was born"
    },
    {
        "question": "484. She ........... by her peers.",
        "options": ["criticized", "criticizes", "was criticized"],
        "correctAnswer": "was criticized"
    },
    {
        "question": "485. The truth ........... from me.",
        "options": ["was hidden", "hid", "hide"],
        "correctAnswer": "was hidden"
    },
    {
        "question": "486. The meeting ........... in the last minute.",
        "options": ["cancelled", "cancel", "was cancelled"],
        "correctAnswer": "was cancelled"
    },
    {
        "question": "487. Your action ........... by the authorities.",
        "options": ["forbade", "forbidden", "was forbidden"],
        "correctAnswer": "was forbidden"
    },
    {
        "question": "488. The meeting date ............ by the committee.",
        "options": ["was confirmed", "confirms", "confirmed"],
        "correctAnswer": "was confirmed"
    },
    {
        "question": "489. I ........... all the truth. You shouldn't have lied to me.",
        "options": ["were known", "knew", "know"],
        "correctAnswer": "knew"
    },
    {
        "question": "490. She ........... by them the first place.",
        "options": ["awarded", "awards", "was awarded"],
        "correctAnswer": "was awarded"
    },
    {
        "question": "491. The soldiers ........... by their enemy.",
        "options": ["attacked", "attack", "were attacked"],
        "correctAnswer": "were attacked"
    },
    {
        "question": "492. All the lessons ...........",
        "options": ["is understood", "were understood", "was understood"],
        "correctAnswer": "were understood"
    },
    {
        "question": "493. This part of information ........... him.",
        "options": ["was shared with", "were shared with", "are shared with"],
        "correctAnswer": "was shared with"
    },
    {
        "question": "494. Her results ........... to all participants.",
        "options": ["were shown", "was shown", "shown"],
        "correctAnswer": "were shown"
    },
    {
        "question": "495. My lost keys ...........",
        "options": ["found", "finds", "were found"],
        "correctAnswer": "were found"
    },
    {
        "question": "496. A new doctrine ........... by them yesterday.",
        "options": ["discussed", "discuss", "was discussed"],
        "correctAnswer": "was discussed"
    },
    {
        "question": "497. Your mistakes ...........",
        "options": ["is considered", "consider", "were considered"],
        "correctAnswer": "were considered"
    },
    {
        "question": "498. Four new houses ...........",
        "options": ["build", "were built", "building"],
        "correctAnswer": "were built"
    },
    {
        "question": "499. His name ....... in the list.",
        "options": ["included", "includes", "was included"],
        "correctAnswer": "was included"
    },
    {
        "question": "500. Her flat ........... by me.",
        "options": ["were bought", "was bought", "bought"],
        "correctAnswer": "was bought"
    },
    {
        "question": "501. It really ............. you.",
        "options": ["help", "helps", "do help"],
        "correctAnswer": "helps"
    },
    {
        "question": "502. They ......... it very well.",
        "options": ["know", "knows", "can knows"],
        "correctAnswer": "know"
    },
    {
        "question": "503. I see they .............. this city.",
        "options": ["like", "likes", "liking"],
        "correctAnswer": "like"
    },
    {
        "question": "504. Unfortunately, it sometimes ...........",
        "options": ["happens", "happen", "hapens"],
        "correctAnswer": "happens"
    },
    {
        "question": "505. She ............ there.",
        "options": ["live", "lifes", "lives"],
        "correctAnswer": "lives"
    },
    {
        "question": "506. We ........... very hard.",
        "options": ["work", "works", "is working"],
        "correctAnswer": "work"
    },
    {
        "question": "507. She .... English fluently.",
        "options": ["speaks", "speak", "spokes"],
        "correctAnswer": "speaks"
    },
    {
        "question": "508. They ........ business.",
        "options": ["does", "do", "doing"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "509. She ........ English at kindergarten.",
        "options": ["study", "studys", "studies"],
        "correctAnswer": "studies"
    },
    {
        "question": "510. I ........... so, too.",
        "options": ["think", "thinks", "are thinking"],
        "correctAnswer": "think"
    },
    {
        "question": "511. The news ........... quite interesting.",
        "options": ["seems", "seem", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "seems"
    },
    {
        "question": "512. My friend ........... a fairly good computer.",
        "options": ["has", "have", "haves"],
        "correctAnswer": "has"
    },
    {
        "question": "513. The ticket ........... 75 pence.",
        "options": ["cost", "costs", "is costing"],
        "correctAnswer": "costs"
    },
    {
        "question": "514. These flats ........... 400,000 dollars.",
        "options": ["cost", "cost", "costed"],
        "correctAnswer": "cost"
    },
    {
        "question": "515. Our new teacher ........... a lot.",
        "options": ["know", "is knowning", "knows"],
        "correctAnswer": "knows"
    },
    {
        "question": "516. This lesson ........... interesting.",
        "options": ["looks", "look", "seem"],
        "correctAnswer": "looks"
    },
    {
        "question": "517. My closest friends ........... this movie.",
        "options": ["likes", "like", "enjoys"],
        "correctAnswer": "like"
    },
    {
        "question": "518. Your girlfriend always ........... interesting things.",
        "options": ["says", "say", "think"],
        "correctAnswer": "says"
    },
    {
        "question": "519. This software ........... very well.",
        "options": ["work", "works", "working"],
        "correctAnswer": "works"
    },
    {
        "question": "520. My sister ........... to university.",
        "options": ["goes", "go", "gone"],
        "correctAnswer": "goes"
    },
    {
        "question": "521. It ........... interest her.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "wasn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "522. She ............. want to do it again.",
        "options": ["don't", "doesn't", "isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "523. I............ believe her.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "am not"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "524. We ............. know what to say.",
        "options": ["don't", "doesn't", "not"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "525. She.............. tell them all the truth.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "526. I ........... know all the information.",
        "options": ["don't", "doesn't", "not"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "527. He ........... have any brothers or sisters.",
        "options": ["don't", "isn't", "doesn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "528. She ........... earn this sum of money.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "529. It ............. help me.",
        "options": ["don't", "doesn't", "isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "530. They ........... believe you.",
        "options": ["don't", "doesn't", "not"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "531. This thing ........... interest me.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "532. Our teacher ........... know what to do.",
        "options": ["don't", "not", "doesn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "533. This situation ........... seem quite strange.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "not"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "534. Most students ........... learn French effectively.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "535. This news ........... seem unusual.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "536. Their lessons ........... start on time.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "hadn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "537. These things ........... seem important.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "538. My results ........... look very good.",
        "options": ["don't", "doesn't", "aren't looking"],
        "correctAnswer": "don't"
    },
    {
        "question": "539. Her husband ........... spend much money.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "540. My boyfriend .......... remember it.",
        "options": ["has", "don't", "doesn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "doesn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "541. ........... he speak English?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "542. ........... you live there?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "543. ........... you agree with us?",
        "options": ["Is", "Does", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "544. ........... you understand me?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "545. ........... we learn Russian effectively?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "546. ........... I show better results?",
        "options": ["Doe", "Have", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "547. ........... it really work?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "548. ........... she support you?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "549. ........... he usually buy cheap or expensive things?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "550. ........... it at times happen?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "551. ........... your grandparents also think so?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "552. ........... his friends think the same?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "553. ........... that thing matter?",
        "options": ["Is", "Do", "Does"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "554. ........... her success motivate you?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "555. ........... all people like this fruit?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "556. ........... your mother do business?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "557. ........... these words inspire you?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "558. ........... your business partner work professionally?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "559. ........... your teacher give you way too much homework?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "560. ........... these projects bring you benefits?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Doesn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "561. ........... their success motivate you?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "562. ........... his parents think so?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "563. ........... all people like it?",
        "options": ["Does", "Have", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "564. ........... your grandfather do business?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "565. ........... those projects bring you benefit?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "566. ........... your business partner work professionally?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "567. ........... this thing really matter for you?",
        "options": ["Don't", "Do", "Does"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "568. ........... your close friends think the same?",
        "options": ["Does", "Do", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "569. ........... these words inspire you?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Doesn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Do"
    },
    {
        "question": "570. ........... your teacher give you way too much homework during the week?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "Don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Does"
    },
    {
        "question": "571. Who ........... you?",
        "options": ["do help", "helps", "aid"],
        "correctAnswer": "helps"
    },
    {
        "question": "572. Who ........... you know?",
        "options": ["do", "does", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "573. What ........... so interesting in your opinion?",
        "options": ["do seem", "seems", "seeming"],
        "correctAnswer": "seems"
    },
    {
        "question": "574. What TV channels ........... you watch?",
        "options": ["do", "does", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "575. Where ............. they live?",
        "options": ["do", "does", "doesn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "576. When .............. it begin?",
        "options": ["do", "is", "does"],
        "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
        "question": "577. How often ........ he go to the gym?",
        "options": ["does", "do", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
        "question": "578. How much ......... it cost?",
        "options": ["do", "does", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
        "question": "579. How many times a month ........... they go swimming?",
        "options": ["do", "does", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "580. How ........... you find this idea?",
        "options": ["does", "do", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "581. How far ........ his parents live?",
        "options": ["does", "are", "do"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "582. Could you tell me how often ........... this thing happen?",
        "options": ["does", "do", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
        "question": "583. Where ........... your cousin work?",
        "options": ["does", "do", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
        "question": "584. What ........... so strange?",
        "options": ["do look", "looks", "are looking"],
        "correctAnswer": "looks"
    },
    {
        "question": "585. What time ........... the lesson finish?",
        "options": ["does", "do", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
        "question": "586. Who ............. it?",
        "options": ["recommends", "do recommend", "does recommend"],
        "correctAnswer": "recommends"
    },
    {
        "question": "587. Where ........... your boyfriend come from?",
        "options": ["does", "do", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
        "question": "588. What kind of advice ........... her work colleagues need?",
        "options": ["does", "are", "do"],
        "correctAnswer": "do"
    },
    {
        "question": "589. How ........... your teacher explain it to you?",
        "options": ["does", "do", "don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
        "question": "590. Why ......... their result seem so bad?",
        "options": ["do", "does", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "does"
    },
    {
        "question": "591. I ........... so happy with you.",
        "options": ["are", "am", "will"],
        "correctAnswer": "am"
    },
    {
        "question": "592. This knowledge ....... enough.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "593. We ........... at their home.",
        "options": ["am", "are", "be"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "594. It ............. fairly interesting.",
        "options": ["are", "is", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "595. She ........... a student.",
        "options": ["aren't being", "are", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "596. You ........... so talented in my opinion.",
        "options": ["are", "have", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "597. She ...... very beautiful tonight.",
        "options": ["were", "is", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "598. They forever say information ........... power.",
        "options": ["have", "is", "mean"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "599. The morning news ........... surprising.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "be"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "600. He ........... our partner.",
        "options": ["were", "have", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "601. You ........... really right.",
        "options": ["isn't", "are", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "602. I ........... happy.",
        "options": ["am being", "am not", "not am"],
        "correctAnswer": "am not"
    },
    {
        "question": "603. They ........... in the office.",
        "options": ["aren't", "isn't", "hasn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "604. We ............. together.",
        "options": ["am not", "are", "am"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "605. She ........... at work.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "606. I ........... tired at all.",
        "options": ["isn't", "am not", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "am not"
    },
    {
        "question": "607. It........... interesting if you ask me.",
        "options": ["aren't", "is", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "608. He .............. with her now.",
        "options": ["being", "aren't", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "609. She ........... a businesswoman.",
        "options": ["aren't", "is", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "610. It ............. rainy.",
        "options": ["are", "is", "seem"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "611. Her knowledge ........... enough.",
        "options": ["is", "aren't", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "612. This thing ............. very important.",
        "options": ["aren't", "is", "seem"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "613. The morning news ......... so good.",
        "options": ["is", "aren't", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "614. That pair of scissors ........... in the kitchen.",
        "options": ["aren't", "isn't", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "615. Her business partners ........... reliable enough.",
        "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "616. My scissors ........... on the desk.",
        "options": ["are", "isn't", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "617. These exams ........... supposed to be difficult.",
        "options": ["isn't", "have", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "618. This joke ........... so funny.",
        "options": ["is", "aren't", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "619. My girlfriend and I ........... in the park.",
        "options": ["am not", "is not", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "620. You should know that money ........... everything.",
        "options": ["aren't", "isn't", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "621. ........... you here for the third time?",
        "options": ["Do", "Are", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "622. ........... they quite bust at the moment?",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "623. ........... she a successful businesswoman?",
        "options": ["Am", "Is", "Did"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "624. ........... he a well known singer?",
        "options": ["Does", "Am", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "625. ........... he a Spanish teacher?",
        "options": ["Is", "Are", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "626. ........... it a good idea or not?",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "627. ........... you satisfied with their results?",
        "options": ["Do", "Are", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "628. ........... I an industrious student?",
        "options": ["Is", "Are", "Am"],
        "correctAnswer": "Am"
    },
    {
        "question": "629. ........... we in the required place?",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "630. ........... it fiercely cold outside?",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "631. ........... this detail really important?",
        "options": ["Is", "Am", "Does"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "632. ........... this chance amazing?",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "633. ........... that hotel too expensive?",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "634. ........ the news surprising for you?",
        "options": ["Aren't", "Are", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "635. ........... their parents at home?",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "636. ........... this knowledge enough?",
        "options": ["Is", "Are", "Aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "637. ........... her bag heavy?",
        "options": ["Am", "Is", "Does"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "638. ........... our behaviour strange?",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Does"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "639. ........... these changes strongly necessary?",
        "options": ["Is", "Do", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "640. ........... these lessons effective?",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "641. How old ........... she?",
        "options": ["are", "is", "does"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "642. What kind of man ........... he?",
        "options": ["is", "am", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "643. Where ........... that place?",
        "options": ["are", "is", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "644. Who ........... there?",
        "options": ["is", "am", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "645. When ...... you free so as to meet?",
        "options": ["are", "is", "do"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "646. Why ........... she so depressed?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "647. How ........... he?",
        "options": ["are", "is", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "648. How often .... you in that building?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "do"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "649. What ........... it in English?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "650. What color ........... that bike?",
        "options": ["are", "is", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "651. Where ...... justice in this country?",
        "options": ["are", "have", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "652. How much ........... this pair of blue trousers?",
        "options": ["are", "is", "does"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "653. What ........... easy for them?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "654. Why ........... these offers interesting?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "be"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "655. Where ........... your new friends from?",
        "options": ["have", "is", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "656. How ........... your recently open business?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "do"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "657. When ........... your boss free?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "does"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "658. What kind of person ........... your work colleague?",
        "options": ["are", "has", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "659. How much ........... these trousers?",
        "options": ["are", "is", "does costs"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "660. Why ........... this laptop so expensive?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "661. He usually ............ up quite early.",
        "options": ["gets", "got", "getting"],
        "correctAnswer": "gets"
    },
    {
        "question": "662. ......... they at the party yesterday?",
        "options": ["Were", "Was", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
        "question": "663. She ........... to him.",
        "options": ["lied", "lay", "laid"],
        "correctAnswer": "lied"
    },
    {
        "question": "664. The last meeting ........... very stressful.",
        "options": ["were", "was", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "665. I often ........... her when I worked there.",
        "options": ["saw", "see", "not saw"],
        "correctAnswer": "saw"
    },
    {
        "question": "666. They met .... last month.",
        "options": ["in", "on", "-"],
        "correctAnswer": "-"
    },
    {
        "question": "667. Our mistakes ........... rather small.",
        "options": ["were", "was", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "668. The pen .... on the grey desk.",
        "options": ["lied", "lay", "lain"],
        "correctAnswer": "lay"
    },
    {
        "question": "669. It ............. to us.",
        "options": ["happening", "happened", "happenned"],
        "correctAnswer": "happened"
    },
    {
        "question": "670. He....... to the party two days ago.",
        "options": ["were", "goes", "went"],
        "correctAnswer": "went"
    },
    {
        "question": "671. We ........... the results of the test.",
        "options": ["seen", "saw", "sees"],
        "correctAnswer": "saw"
    },
    {
        "question": "672. I........... it perfectly.",
        "options": ["known", "knew", "knowing"],
        "correctAnswer": "knew"
    },
    {
        "question": "673. He ........... up very early.",
        "options": ["get", "got", "raises"],
        "correctAnswer": "got"
    },
    {
        "question": "674. They ........... so many questions.",
        "options": ["have", "had", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "had"
    },
    {
        "question": "675. I ........... her letter.",
        "options": ["got", "gotten", "receive"],
        "correctAnswer": "got"
    },
    {
        "question": "676. She ........... a day off yesterday.",
        "options": ["have", "has", "had"],
        "correctAnswer": "had"
    },
    {
        "question": "677. He ........... the correct answer.",
        "options": ["know", "knew", "don't know"],
        "correctAnswer": "knew"
    },
    {
        "question": "678. Their results .......... good enough.",
        "options": ["was", "were", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "679. She ........... her mistake at last.",
        "options": ["saw", "seen", "sees"],
        "correctAnswer": "saw"
    },
    {
        "question": "680. Your idea ........... absolutely brilliant.",
        "options": ["were", "was", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "681. She ........... it loudly enough.",
        "options": ["say", "said", "has says"],
        "correctAnswer": "said"
    },
    {
        "question": "682. He ........... better that day.",
        "options": ["feel", "felt", "fall"],
        "correctAnswer": "felt"
    },
    {
        "question": "683. They often ........... mistakes.",
        "options": ["makes", "made", "do"],
        "correctAnswer": "made"
    },
    {
        "question": "684. She ........... everything correctly.",
        "options": ["did", "do", "tries"],
        "correctAnswer": "did"
    },
    {
        "question": "685. You ........... much better.",
        "options": ["feeling", "felt", "is way too"],
        "correctAnswer": "felt"
    },
    {
        "question": "686. I ........... them the information.",
        "options": ["said", "told", "say"],
        "correctAnswer": "told"
    },
    {
        "question": "687. She finally ........... me all the truth.",
        "options": ["told", "said", "will tell"],
        "correctAnswer": "told"
    },
    {
        "question": "688. She ........... them an offer.",
        "options": ["did", "made", "does"],
        "correctAnswer": "made"
    },
    {
        "question": "689. They ........... it again that night.",
        "options": ["says", "had said", "said"],
        "correctAnswer": "said"
    },
    {
        "question": "690. She ........... an enormous mistake.",
        "options": ["made", "did", "makes"],
        "correctAnswer": "made"
    },
    {
        "question": "691. He ........... his mistakes at last.",
        "options": ["see", "saw", "recognize"],
        "correctAnswer": "saw"
    },
    {
        "question": "692. He ........... to that special conference on time.",
        "options": ["come", "came", "doesn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "came"
    },
    {
        "question": "693. The thing is that I ........... the same.",
        "options": ["to think", "thought", "thinking"],
        "correctAnswer": "thought"
    },
    {
        "question": "694. Their boss ........... differently.",
        "options": ["thought", "think", "don't think"],
        "correctAnswer": "thought"
    },
    {
        "question": "695. He ........... to the party later.",
        "options": ["come", "don't come", "came"],
        "correctAnswer": "came"
    },
    {
        "question": "696. They ........... jogging the day before yesterday.",
        "options": ["went", "gone", "have been"],
        "correctAnswer": "went"
    },
    {
        "question": "697. I ........... her brother last week.",
        "options": ["saw", "seen", "haven't saw"],
        "correctAnswer": "saw"
    },
    {
        "question": "698. She ........... to the park with him yesterday.",
        "options": ["goes", "went", "has been going"],
        "correctAnswer": "went"
    },
    {
        "question": "699. My friend ........... the first place at the mountain biking contest.",
        "options": ["taken", "took", "take"],
        "correctAnswer": "took"
    },
    {
        "question": "700. It ........ me one hour to get to that awful place.",
        "options": ["took", "taken", "took from"],
        "correctAnswer": "took"
    },
    {
        "question": "701. He ........... all the information they needed.",
        "options": ["found", "find", "don't find"],
        "correctAnswer": "found"
    },
    {
        "question": "702. She ........... a successful businesswoman.",
        "options": ["become", "became", "will became"],
        "correctAnswer": "became"
    },
    {
        "question": "703. He ........... him 300 dollars yesterday.",
        "options": ["give", "gave", "have given"],
        "correctAnswer": "gave"
    },
    {
        "question": "704. They ........... fairly famous.",
        "options": ["isn't", "becomes", "became"],
        "correctAnswer": "became"
    },
    {
        "question": "705. I ........... it online while searching for something else.",
        "options": ["find", "found", "have been finding"],
        "correctAnswer": "found"
    },
    {
        "question": "706. We ........... our money in a local bank.",
        "options": ["keeps", "kept", "doesn't keep"],
        "correctAnswer": "kept"
    },
    {
        "question": "707. Our colleague ........... it near the computer.",
        "options": ["put", "to put", "have put"],
        "correctAnswer": "put"
    },
    {
        "question": "708. They ........... our little secret.",
        "options": ["keeps", "kept", "didn't kept"],
        "correctAnswer": "kept"
    },
    {
        "question": "709. She ........... him one more chance.",
        "options": ["given", "gave", "giving"],
        "correctAnswer": "gave"
    },
    {
        "question": "710. He ........... it on the desk.",
        "options": ["putting", "put", "has put"],
        "correctAnswer": "put"
    },
    {
        "question": "711. They ........... the latest news.",
        "options": ["hear", "heard", "heared"],
        "correctAnswer": "heard"
    },
    {
        "question": "712. It ........... his abilities two days ago.",
        "options": ["show", "shown", "showed"],
        "correctAnswer": "showed"
    },
    {
        "question": "713. That thing ........ a lot to us.",
        "options": ["mean", "meant", "don't mean"],
        "correctAnswer": "meant"
    },
    {
        "question": "714. It ........... me how professional they were.",
        "options": ["show", "showed", "have showed"],
        "correctAnswer": "showed"
    },
    {
        "question": "715. Our conference ........... much later than expected.",
        "options": ["began", "begun", "is beginning"],
        "correctAnswer": "began"
    },
    {
        "question": "716. She ........... Russia last year.",
        "options": ["leave", "left", "will leave"],
        "correctAnswer": "left"
    },
    {
        "question": "717. I ........ it for the first time. I was surprised.",
        "options": ["hearing", "heard", "am hearing"],
        "correctAnswer": "heard"
    },
    {
        "question": "718. It ........ t .............. the following thing.",
        "options": ["meant", "mean", "meaning"],
        "correctAnswer": "meant"
    },
    {
        "question": "719. I ........... my bag at home unfortunately.",
        "options": ["leaves", "left", "forget"],
        "correctAnswer": "left"
    },
    {
        "question": "720. The conference ........... on time.",
        "options": ["begin", "begun", "began"],
        "correctAnswer": "began"
    },
    {
        "question": "721. They ........... in the sea.",
        "options": ["swims", "swam", "swum"],
        "correctAnswer": "swam"
    },
    {
        "question": "722. I........... for this service.",
        "options": ["pays", "paid", "has to pay"],
        "correctAnswer": "paid"
    },
    {
        "question": "723. The company ........... for the goods and services.",
        "options": ["paid", "pay", "payed"],
        "correctAnswer": "paid"
    },
    {
        "question": "724. His assistant manager ........... his correspondence.",
        "options": ["to read", "read", "readed"],
        "correctAnswer": "read"
    },
    {
        "question": "725. He ........... you very well.",
        "options": ["understand", "understood", "have understood"],
        "correctAnswer": "understood"
    },
    {
        "question": "726. We ........... in the ocean that day.",
        "options": ["swum", "swam", "swim"],
        "correctAnswer": "swam"
    },
    {
        "question": "727. They ...... everything immediately.",
        "options": ["understood", "understands", "understanded"],
        "correctAnswer": "understood"
    },
    {
        "question": "728. She ........... him a letter.",
        "options": ["wrote", "written", "write"],
        "correctAnswer": "wrote"
    },
    {
        "question": "729. His girlfriend ........... a long letter to him. It was something bad.",
        "options": ["write", "writes", "wrote"],
        "correctAnswer": "wrote"
    },
    {
        "question": "730. Finally, he ........... her letter.",
        "options": ["read", "reading", "have read"],
        "correctAnswer": "read"
    },
    {
        "question": "731. The price ........ sharply yesterday.",
        "options": ["fall", "fell", "fallen"],
        "correctAnswer": "fell"
    },
    {
        "question": "732. I........... her a billet-doux.",
        "options": ["sends", "sent", "sending"],
        "correctAnswer": "sent"
    },
    {
        "question": "733. She ........... down.",
        "options": ["fell", "fallen", "falled"],
        "correctAnswer": "fell"
    },
    {
        "question": "734. I........... up in Europe.",
        "options": ["grown", "grew", "have grew"],
        "correctAnswer": "grew"
    },
    {
        "question": "735. She ........... behind him waiting for something.",
        "options": ["stand", "stood", "standing"],
        "correctAnswer": "stood"
    },
    {
        "question": "736. My grandmother ........ vegetables in her own garden.",
        "options": ["grow", "grew", "grown"],
        "correctAnswer": "grew"
    },
    {
        "question": "737. He ........ her flowers last week.",
        "options": ["send", "sent", "have sent"],
        "correctAnswer": "sent"
    },
    {
        "question": "738. They ........... English.",
        "options": ["speaks", "spoke", "doesn't speak"],
        "correctAnswer": "spoke"
    },
    {
        "question": "739. She ........... Italian.",
        "options": ["spoke", "speak", "don't speak"],
        "correctAnswer": "spoke"
    },
    {
        "question": "740. I........... up.",
        "options": ["stands", "stood", "had stood"],
        "correctAnswer": "stood"
    },
    {
        "question": "741. They ........... so beautifully.",
        "options": ["sang", "sung", "singing"],
        "correctAnswer": "sang"
    },
    {
        "question": "742. I ....... more than 15 kilometers.",
        "options": ["ran", "runs", "could ran"],
        "correctAnswer": "ran"
    },
    {
        "question": "743. She ........... to call my uncle.",
        "options": ["forget", "have forgot", "forgot"],
        "correctAnswer": "forgot"
    },
    {
        "question": "744. Her parents ........... her go to the party.",
        "options": ["let", "letting", "doesn't let"],
        "correctAnswer": "let"
    },
    {
        "question": "745. I........... to lock the front door.",
        "options": ["forgotten", "forgot", "has forgotten"],
        "correctAnswer": "forgot"
    },
    {
        "question": "746. Her mother ....... him stay at home.",
        "options": ["to let", "let", "letting"],
        "correctAnswer": "let"
    },
    {
        "question": "747. I........... down.",
        "options": ["sat", "sitting", "sits"],
        "correctAnswer": "sat"
    },
    {
        "question": "748. The old lady ......... in an armchair.",
        "options": ["sitting", "sat", "have sat"],
        "correctAnswer": "sat"
    },
    {
        "question": "749. She ........... very fast.",
        "options": ["run", "don't run", "ran"],
        "correctAnswer": "ran"
    },
    {
        "question": "750. You .... professionally.",
        "options": ["sang", "sung", "doesn't sing"],
        "correctAnswer": "sang"
    },
    {
        "question": "751. He ........... a couple of sandwiches.",
        "options": ["eaten", "ate", "eat"],
        "correctAnswer": "ate"
    },
    {
        "question": "752. They ........... the correct answer.",
        "options": ["chose", "chosen", "choice"],
        "correctAnswer": "chose"
    },
    {
        "question": "753. She ........... too much.",
        "options": ["eating", "ate", "don't eat"],
        "correctAnswer": "ate"
    },
    {
        "question": "754. She ........ very expensive clothes.",
        "options": ["bought", "buy", "buying"],
        "correctAnswer": "bought"
    },
    {
        "question": "755. My business partner ........ all the goods yesterday.",
        "options": ["sell", "sold", "have sold"],
        "correctAnswer": "sold"
    },
    {
        "question": "756. Unfortunately, he .... his leg.",
        "options": ["broken", "broke", "have broken"],
        "correctAnswer": "broke"
    },
    {
        "question": "757. Tom ........... a new flat.",
        "options": ["buy", "buyed", "bought"],
        "correctAnswer": "bought"
    },
    {
        "question": "758. My classmate .... the third answer.",
        "options": ["choose", "chose", "chosen"],
        "correctAnswer": "chose"
    },
    {
        "question": "759. Her car ........... down.",
        "options": ["break", "broke", "breaking"],
        "correctAnswer": "broke"
    },
    {
        "question": "760. She ........ her apartment.",
        "options": ["sold", "sell", "have sold"],
        "correctAnswer": "sold"
    },
    {
        "question": "761. She ........... a lot yesterday.",
        "options": ["sleep", "slept", "sleeped"],
        "correctAnswer": "slept"
    },
    {
        "question": "762. They ........... it away.",
        "options": ["threw", "throw", "thrown"],
        "correctAnswer": "threw"
    },
    {
        "question": "763. I....... them the ball.",
        "options": ["thrown", "threw", "throwing"],
        "correctAnswer": "threw"
    },
    {
        "question": "764. He ........... a glass of orange juice.",
        "options": ["drink", "drank", "drunk"],
        "correctAnswer": "drank"
    },
    {
        "question": "765. After the party, she ........ like a baby.",
        "options": ["sleep", "slept", "sleeped"],
        "correctAnswer": "slept"
    },
    {
        "question": "766. The shoes ......... about 50 dollars.",
        "options": ["costed", "costing", "cost"],
        "correctAnswer": "cost"
    },
    {
        "question": "767. The dress ........... less than she expected.",
        "options": ["costing", "cost", "is costing"],
        "correctAnswer": "cost"
    },
    {
        "question": "768. She ......... a small house on that land.",
        "options": ["build", "built", "have built"],
        "correctAnswer": "built"
    },
    {
        "question": "769. The engineers ........... a high building.",
        "options": ["built", "builds", "has built"],
        "correctAnswer": "built"
    },
    {
        "question": "770. I ........... a glass of milk before going to bed.",
        "options": ["drunk", "drank", "drinks"],
        "correctAnswer": "drank"
    },
    {
        "question": "771. Her advice ........... me much.",
        "options": ["didn't help", "wasn't help", "haven't helped"],
        "correctAnswer": "didn't help"
    },
    {
        "question": "772. I........... free time at all then.",
        "options": ["didn't have", "didn't had", "couldn't had"],
        "correctAnswer": "didn't have"
    },
    {
        "question": "773. My boyfriend ........ to the gym two days ago.",
        "options": ["wasn't go", "didn't go", "weren't go"],
        "correctAnswer": "didn't go"
    },
    {
        "question": "774. She ........... what to say.",
        "options": ["didn't knew", "don't know", "didn't know"],
        "correctAnswer": "didn't know"
    },
    {
        "question": "775. They ............ out help back then.",
        "options": ["didn't needed", "didn't need", "hasn't need"],
        "correctAnswer": "didn't need"
    },
    {
        "question": "776. Honestly, I ........... feel happy.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "didn't", "doesn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "didn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "777. He ........... ask us that question.",
        "options": ["didn't", "wasn't", "don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "didn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "778. He ........... her yesterday.",
        "options": ["didn't call", "haven't call", "didn't called"],
        "correctAnswer": "didn't call"
    },
    {
        "question": "779. They ........... the exams.",
        "options": ["don't passed", "haven't pass", "didn't pass"],
        "correctAnswer": "didn't pass"
    },
    {
        "question": "780. My close friends ........ to that party.",
        "options": ["weren't go", "didn't go", "wasn't go"],
        "correctAnswer": "didn't go"
    },
    {
        "question": "781. ........... she become so famous?",
        "options": ["Did", "Was", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Did"
    },
    {
        "question": "782. Did he ........ all these new words?",
        "options": ["learned", "learn", "learnt"],
        "correctAnswer": "learn"
    },
    {
        "question": "783. ........... you continue buying this kind of perfumes?",
        "options": ["Was", "Did", "Were"],
        "correctAnswer": "Did"
    },
    {
        "question": "784. Did you ........... tired after doing so much work?",
        "options": ["got", "get", "became"],
        "correctAnswer": "get"
    },
    {
        "question": "785. ........... they agree with you?",
        "options": ["Were", "Was", "Did"],
        "correctAnswer": "Did"
    },
    {
        "question": "786. Did it ........... them greatly?",
        "options": ["interested", "interest", "interesting"],
        "correctAnswer": "interest"
    },
    {
        "question": "787. Did it ........... to you too?",
        "options": ["happen", "happened", "happenned"],
        "correctAnswer": "happen"
    },
    {
        "question": "788. ........... they meet for the first time?",
        "options": ["Did", "Were", "Was"],
        "correctAnswer": "Did"
    },
    {
        "question": "789. ........... she pay for everything?",
        "options": ["Was", "Did", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Did"
    },
    {
        "question": "790. ........... you tell her our secret?",
        "options": ["Was", "Did", "Were"],
        "correctAnswer": "Did"
    },
    {
        "question": "791. How ........... you pay for the smartphone?",
        "options": ["was", "did", "-"],
        "correctAnswer": "did"
    },
    {
        "question": "792. What ........... he say?",
        "options": ["-", "was", "did"],
        "correctAnswer": "did"
    },
    {
        "question": "793. ........... two hours ago?",
        "options": ["Who did you call", "Who you called"],
        "correctAnswer": "Who did you call"
    },
    {
        "question": "794. Why ........... she continue learning English there?",
        "options": ["did", "was", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "did"
    },
    {
        "question": "795. How ........... money did you earn that month?",
        "options": ["many", "much", "lot"],
        "correctAnswer": "much"
    },
    {
        "question": "796. ........... from him?",
        "options": ["What you heard", "What did you hear"],
        "correctAnswer": "What did you hear"
    },
    {
        "question": "797. ........... so funny that you burst into laughing?",
        "options": ["What did seem", "What seemed"],
        "correctAnswer": "What seemed"
    },
    {
        "question": "798. Where ......... the accident happen?",
        "options": ["did", "was", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "did"
    },
    {
        "question": "799. ........... at the party?",
        "options": ["Who did arrived", "Who arrived"],
        "correctAnswer": "Who arrived"
    },
    {
        "question": "800. How ........... mistakes did he make?",
        "options": ["much", "many", "a lot"],
        "correctAnswer": "many"
    },
    {
        "question": "801. It ........... a really good idea.",
        "options": ["were", "was", "have been"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "802. They ........... with us at the pawn shop.",
        "options": ["was", "has been", "were"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "803. I hate to admit it but you ........... absolutely right.",
        "options": ["was", "were", "believe"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "804. Hearing that, he ........... really surprised.",
        "options": ["was", "were", "be"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "805. Yesterday I ........... so happy.",
        "options": ["were", "was being", "was"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "806. I want to play it again! It ........... such a wonderful game.",
        "options": ["was", "were", "have been"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "807. Seeing the offer, we ........... interested in their products.",
        "options": ["was", "were", "be"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "808. She ........... really distressed.",
        "options": ["were", "was", "look"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "809. Unfortunately, they ........... late.",
        "options": ["don't", "was", "were"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "810. He ........... so disappointed.",
        "options": ["weren't", "was", "look"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "811. To his surprise, the news ........... shocking.",
        "options": ["were", "was", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "812. The answer to that problem ........... very simple.",
        "options": ["was", "were", "seem"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "813. You know that his parents ........... poor.",
        "options": ["is", "was", "were"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "814. That detail ........... fairly important.",
        "options": ["have been", "was", "weren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "815. After studying the lesson again, their results ........... much better.",
        "options": ["was", "has been", "were"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "816. Her result ........... excellent.",
        "options": ["was", "have been", "weren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "817. Our money ........ enough to buy it.",
        "options": ["were", "was", "have been"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "818. Everybody believed that the game ........... so exciting.",
        "options": ["have been", "were", "was"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "819. Her aunt ........... very rich.",
        "options": ["were", "be", "was"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "820. Her questions ........... really strange.",
        "options": ["were", "was", "look"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "821. Your brother ........... a bad worker.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "weren't", "were"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "822. You ........... really sure.",
        "options": ["weren't", "wasn't", "isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "weren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "823. I ........... satisfied with their short answer.",
        "options": ["aren't", "wasn't", "weren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "824. We ........... ready for that flooding.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "has been", "weren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "weren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "825. They ........... our best friends.",
        "options": ["weren't", "was", "wasn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "weren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "826. She ........... among the thieves.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "weren't", "have been"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "827. It ....... her personal achievement.",
        "options": ["weren't", "wasn't", "were"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "828. He ........... my best friend.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "were", "have been"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "829. I think it ...... the right choice.",
        "options": ["weren't", "hasn't", "wasn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "830. It ....... a bad example.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "were", "haven't been"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "831. These measures ........... really necessary.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "weren't", "hasn't been"],
        "correctAnswer": "weren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "832. Her decision ........... unexpected as you thought.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "weren't", "haven't been"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "833. All his threats ........... serious.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "is very", "were"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "834. Their trip .............. long enough.",
        "options": ["weren't", "wasn't", "hadn't been"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "835. Her employees ....... professional.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "can being", "weren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "weren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "836. The interview ........... easy for us.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "have been", "didn't was"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "837. This song ......... popular that time.",
        "options": ["weren't", "wasn't", "isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "838. Her problem ........... big.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "weren't", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "839. Although he considers otherwise, this result ........... a big success.",
        "options": ["weren't", "aren't", "wasn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "840. I must say: English ........... easy for me.",
        "options": ["wasn't", "aren't", "weren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "wasn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "841. ........... it expensive?",
        "options": ["Are", "Was", "Were"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "842. ........... she the best worker?",
        "options": ["Were", "Was", "Does"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "843. ........... he your colleague?",
        "options": ["Were", "Are", "Was"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "844. ........... it a popular trend then?",
        "options": ["Was", "Were", "Did"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "845. ........... I badly mistaken?",
        "options": ["Did", "Was", "Were"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "846. ........... they financially independent?",
        "options": ["Were", "Does", "Was"],
        "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
        "question": "847. ........... you in Russia last year?",
        "options": ["Was", "Have", "Were"],
        "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
        "question": "848. ........... we on the right way or not?",
        "options": ["Was", "Were", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
        "question": "849. ........... I in the right place?",
        "options": ["Was", "Have", "Were"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "850. ........... it your new idea?",
        "options": ["Were", "Was", "Did"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "851. ........... this knowledge basic?",
        "options": ["Did", "Was", "Were"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "852. ........... his wife pregnant?",
        "options": ["Was", "Were", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "853. ........... these mistakes serious?",
        "options": ["Was", "Did", "Were"],
        "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
        "question": "854. ........... this information very important?",
        "options": ["Was", "Were", "Did"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "855. ........... our advice helpful?",
        "options": ["Were", "Did", "Was"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "856. ........... your competitors really so strong?",
        "options": ["Has", "Were", "Was"],
        "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
        "question": "857. ........... the tasks difficult?",
        "options": ["Were", "Was", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
        "question": "858. ........... this song so popular?",
        "options": ["Were", "Was", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "859. ........... her results different?",
        "options": ["Was", "Were", "Did"],
        "correctAnswer": "Were"
    },
    {
        "question": "860. ........... your boss available three days ago?",
        "options": ["Did", "Has", "Was"],
        "correctAnswer": "Was"
    },
    {
        "question": "861. What kind if offer ........... that?",
        "options": ["are", "was", "were"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "862. Why ........... she so angry with me?",
        "options": ["were", "did", "was"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "863. How ........... he?",
        "options": ["did", "was", "were"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "864. How old ........... you when you studied at that faculty?",
        "options": ["were", "was", "did"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "865. Where ........... you?",
        "options": ["was", "were", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "866. What ........... so annoying?",
        "options": ["were", "was", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "867. How interested in the project ........... they?",
        "options": ["was", "have", "were"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "868. Why ........... they so annoyed yesterday?",
        "options": ["was", "were", "did"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "869. What ........... on the floor?",
        "options": ["were", "did", "was"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "870. How surprised ........... she seeing them?",
        "options": ["was", "were", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "871. How much knowledge in that lesson ........... truly useful?",
        "options": ["are", "has", "was"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "872. How enthusiastic ........... you English business partner?",
        "options": ["was", "were", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "873. How long ........... the way to the mall?",
        "options": ["were", "did", "was"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "874. When ........... her students ready for the exam?",
        "options": ["was", "were", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "875. Where ........... the keys?",
        "options": ["were", "was", "did"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "876. Why ........... you boss so interested in our project?",
        "options": ["has", "were", "was"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "877. How interested ........... the employees in her project?",
        "options": ["was", "were", "did"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "878. Where ........... your parents last week?",
        "options": ["were", "was", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "were"
    },
    {
        "question": "879. How ........... the party?",
        "options": ["were", "was", "did"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "880. How much money ........... there?",
        "options": ["were", "was", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "was"
    },
    {
        "question": "881. He will ........... to do it.",
        "options": ["order s", "order", "ordering"],
        "correctAnswer": "order"
    },
    {
        "question": "882. Don't worry. I'm sure this flat will ........... you.",
        "options": ["suit", "suits", "suit not"],
        "correctAnswer": "suit"
    },
    {
        "question": "883. I deeply hope she will ........... smoking.",
        "options": ["stops", "stopped", "stop"],
        "correctAnswer": "stop"
    },
    {
        "question": "884. She ........... invite them to the party.",
        "options": ["shall", "will", "wouldn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "885. He will ........... this awkward situation.",
        "options": ["control", "controls", "controlling"],
        "correctAnswer": "control"
    },
    {
        "question": "886. I think she will ........... about that problem again.",
        "options": ["complaining", "complains", "complain"],
        "correctAnswer": "complain"
    },
    {
        "question": "887. Our manager will ........... her opinion later.",
        "options": ["form", "expresses", "forms"],
        "correctAnswer": "form"
    },
    {
        "question": "888. The song ........... popular.",
        "options": ["will", "shall", "would"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "889. Don't panic. I will ........... the document.",
        "options": ["saves", "saved", "save"],
        "correctAnswer": "save"
    },
    {
        "question": "890. My colleagues and I ........... debate this problem later.",
        "options": ["shall", "will", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "891. Her parents won't ........... an apartment this year.",
        "options": ["bought", "buys", "buy"],
        "correctAnswer": "buy"
    },
    {
        "question": "892. She ........... explain all rules.",
        "options": ["want", "won't", "isn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "won't"
    },
    {
        "question": "893. They ........... share this information with me.",
        "options": ["will", "want", "won"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "894. I think she ........... agree with these principles.",
        "options": ["want", "won't", "will"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "895. My sister ........... celebrate her birthday with her friends this year.",
        "options": ["want", "will don't", "will"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "896. They won't ........... a better offer.",
        "options": ["make", "makes", "not make"],
        "correctAnswer": "make"
    },
    {
        "question": "897. It ........... satisfy your demands.",
        "options": ["want", "won't", "don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "won't"
    },
    {
        "question": "898. We ........... to inform the chief executive tomorrow.",
        "options": ["won't", "want", "will"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "899. Let's hope that our director won't ........... these changes.",
        "options": ["notice", "notices", "not notice"],
        "correctAnswer": "notice"
    },
    {
        "question": "900. Her classmate won't ........... at her.",
        "options": ["laughs", "not laugh", "laugh"],
        "correctAnswer": "laugh"
    },
    {
        "question": "901. Will they ........... something really tasty?",
        "options": ["cook", "cooking", "cooks"],
        "correctAnswer": "cook"
    },
    {
        "question": "902. Hey, mister! ........... it take us more time to get to this place?",
        "options": ["Do", "Does", "will"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "903. ........... she offer more money for the job?",
        "options": ["Does", "Will", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Will"
    },
    {
        "question": "904. ........... your business partners supply all the goods tomorrow?",
        "options": ["Will", "Do", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Will"
    },
    {
        "question": "905. ........... the professor correct out mistakes?",
        "options": ["Do", "Will", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Will"
    },
    {
        "question": "906. Will her parents ........... a new house?",
        "options": ["building", "builds", "build"],
        "correctAnswer": "build"
    },
    {
        "question": "907. ........ it cost more tomorrow?",
        "options": ["Will", "Do", "Could"],
        "correctAnswer": "Will"
    },
    {
        "question": "908. Will the firm ........... bankrupt?",
        "options": ["goes", "gone", "go"],
        "correctAnswer": "go"
    },
    {
        "question": "909. Will he ........ making the same mistakes again and again?",
        "options": ["continue", "continues", "continuing"],
        "correctAnswer": "continue"
    },
    {
        "question": "910. ........... she start breaking the rules again?",
        "options": ["Is", "Does", "Will"],
        "correctAnswer": "Will"
    },
    {
        "question": "911. How long will it .............. us to get there?",
        "options": ["takes", "take", "taking"],
        "correctAnswer": "take"
    },
    {
        "question": "912. Do you know why he will ........... there an hour later?",
        "options": ["arrive", "arrives", "get"],
        "correctAnswer": "arrive"
    },
    {
        "question": "913. How surprised ...........?",
        "options": ["will be our classmates", "will our classmates be", "our classmates be will"],
        "correctAnswer": "will our classmates be"
    },
    {
        "question": "914. What kind of challenge will she ...........?",
        "options": ["faces", "faced", "face"],
        "correctAnswer": "face"
    },
    {
        "question": "915. How long ........... she be away?",
        "options": ["is", "will", "do"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "916. Which answer ........... be better?",
        "options": ["does", "don't", "will"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "917. Where ........... the party take place?",
        "options": ["will", "is", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "918. What questions ........... you ask?",
        "options": ["will be", "are", "will"],
        "correctAnswer": "will"
    },
    {
        "question": "919. How interesting ...........?",
        "options": ["will the party be", "will be the party", "the party will be"],
        "correctAnswer": "will the party be"
    },
    {
        "question": "920. Who will ..... this though decision?",
        "options": ["takes", "take", "taking"],
        "correctAnswer": "take"
    },
    {
        "question": "921. I ........... looking at this slide now.",
        "options": ["am", "are", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "am"
    },
    {
        "question": "922. She ........... having quite big problems now.",
        "options": ["are", "aren't", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "923. They are ........... intensively.",
        "options": ["training", "train", "trainning"],
        "correctAnswer": "training"
    },
    {
        "question": "924. I am ........... my point of view on this issue.",
        "options": ["express", "expressing", "expressed"],
        "correctAnswer": "expressing"
    },
    {
        "question": "925. I see that she ........... lying to us now. Don't you think?",
        "options": ["will", "is", "can"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "926. We are ........... to her favorite song.",
        "options": ["listened", "listen", "listening"],
        "correctAnswer": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question": "927. He ............. teaching them how to spell correctly now.",
        "options": ["are", "is", "am"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "928. I like that you ........... explaining these rules clearly enough for me.",
        "options": ["are", "is", "am"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "929. Pay attention! It ........... happening right now!",
        "options": ["are", "can", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "930. He is ........... to her speech.",
        "options": ["listening", "listen", "listenning"],
        "correctAnswer": "listening"
    },
    {
        "question": "931. Children ........... drawing such funny pictures.",
        "options": ["is", "do", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "932. The patient ........... breathing slowly, which is weird.",
        "options": ["does", "is", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "933. The manager ........... calculating their losses.",
        "options": ["are", "has", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "934. The boys ........... painting the fence.",
        "options": ["is", "have", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "935. The owners ........... risking losing all money.",
        "options": ["are", "is", "do"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "936. The wind ........... blowing strongly.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "can"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "937. The police ......... investigating the crime.",
        "options": ["is", "are", "am"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "938. Their business ........... expanding rapidly.",
        "options": ["are", "does", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "939. The sun ........... shining brightly now.",
        "options": ["is", "does", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "940. My boyfriend ........... practicing speaking English now.",
        "options": ["are", "does", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "941. They ........... smoking now.",
        "options": ["doesn't", "don't", "aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "942. She .... conducting this kind of experiment these days.",
        "options": ["aren't", "am not", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "943. He ........... advertising this company.",
        "options": ["isn't", "doesn't", "don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "944. They ........... criticizing her at the moment.",
        "options": ["isn't", "aren't", "does"],
        "correctAnswer": "aren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "945. It ........... bringing any good results now.",
        "options": ["is", "aren't", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "946. Unfortunately, ........... she celebrating her birthday.",
        "options": ["aren't", "does", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "947. We .... joking now. Be silent!",
        "options": ["aren't", "don't", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "948. As far as I know, they ........... dating.",
        "options": ["don't", "isn't", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "949. My opinion is that you ........... wasting time now.",
        "options": ["do", "are", "keeps"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "950. I ........... lying to you!",
        "options": ["am not", "are not", "is not"],
        "correctAnswer": "am not"
    },
    {
        "question": "951. As far as I'm concerned, his students ........... learning English effectively.",
        "options": ["are", "isn't", "don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "952. My parents ........... thinking about this problem right now.",
        "options": ["don't", "are", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "953. My girlfriend and I ........... talking on the phone now.",
        "options": ["don't", "couldn't be", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "954. My business partner............ experiencing any serious difficulties.",
        "options": ["aren't", "is", "don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "955. She ....... preparing for such a difficult exam, which is really strange.",
        "options": ["is", "aren't", "doesn't"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "956. The guests ........... leaving right now. You can close the door.",
        "options": ["are", "don't", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "957. Having said that, his colleagues ........... helping him now.",
        "options": ["don't", "isn't", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "958. The scientist ........... using this method now to test you product.",
        "options": ["aren't", "is", "don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "959. My boyfriend ........... training a lot these days. He's feeling bad.",
        "options": ["aren't", "isn't", "don't"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't"
    },
    {
        "question": "960. Her workers ........... trying to improve their performance.",
        "options": ["are", "don't", "haven't"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "961. ........... you waiting for us?",
        "options": ["Do", "Are", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "962. ........... they losing the game?",
        "options": ["Do", "Have", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "963. ........... she fighting very bravely?",
        "options": ["Is", "Does", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "964. ........... it becoming more and more expensive to live in this town?",
        "options": ["Does", "Are", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "965. ........... he using your phone?",
        "options": ["Are", "Does", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "966. ........... she making a mistake?",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "967. Sorry to interrupt.............. they doing business now?",
        "options": ["Can", "Is", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "968. Hey! Have a look! ........... it raining?",
        "options": ["Is", "Has", "Does"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "969. ........... they comparing their results?",
        "options": ["Have", "Are", "Do"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "970. ........... I spelling it correctly? Please correct me if I'm wrong.",
        "options": ["Are", "Is", "Am"],
        "correctAnswer": "Am"
    },
    {
        "question": "971. ........... your friends chatting online right now?",
        "options": ["Do", "Is", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "972. ........... her partner experiencing big problems now?",
        "options": ["Is", "Does", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "973. ........... the situation getting better these days?",
        "options": ["Do", "Is", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "974. ........... your classmates skiing during this winter?",
        "options": ["Do", "Are", "Have"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "975. ........... your parents talking now about what you've done?",
        "options": ["Do", "Have", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "976. ........... your teacher still waiting for us?",
        "options": ["Does", "Is", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "977. ........... your cousin waiting for us?",
        "options": ["Is", "Has", "Does"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "978. ........... these things becoming uncontrollable or is just my impression?",
        "options": ["Do", "Are", "Is"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "979. ........... her lessons becoming more and more interesting or not?",
        "options": ["Do", "Have", "Are"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are"
    },
    {
        "question": "980. ........... this awesome project bringing you good money now?",
        "options": ["Does", "Is", "Has"],
        "correctAnswer": "Is"
    },
    {
        "question": "981. How ........... he preparing for this hard exam?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "982. Where ........... it happening now?",
        "options": ["does", "are", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "983. I don't understand........... What ........... she trying to say?",
        "options": ["does", "is", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "984. Hey! Sorry to disrupt........... Why ........... they protesting?",
        "options": ["do", "are", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "985. Who ........... waiting for you now? Huh?",
        "options": ["are", "is", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "986. Which strategy ........... you following? Can't you see that it's pointless?",
        "options": ["are", "do", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "987. What issue.........they discussing?",
        "options": ["do", "have", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "988. Why ........... you learning English so intensively? Do you intend to get a better job?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "989. Who ........... calling?",
        "options": ["has", "am", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "990. Where ........... it taking place? Downtown or in the outskirts?",
        "options": ["does", "is", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "991. Where ........... you friends having a great time now? In the mountains?",
        "options": ["am", "is", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "992. What ........... the girl trying to memorize?",
        "options": ["has", "does", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "993. Where ........... your boyfriend earning so much money from?",
        "options": ["has", "is", "does"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "994. Sound the alarm! Why ........... the situation changing?",
        "options": ["is", "do", "are"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "995. How ........... the managers comparing our results these days?",
        "options": ["is", "are", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "996. Who ........... listening to her misleading stories?",
        "options": ["has", "does", "is"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "997. How interesting ........... your Economics professor explaining it?",
        "options": ["does", "is", "has"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "998. Why ........... their teacher telling them these stupid things?",
        "options": ["is", "has", "can"],
        "correctAnswer": "is"
    },
    {
        "question": "999. This is a long log. How ........... the experts measuring it?",
        "options": ["could", "are", "have"],
        "correctAnswer": "are"
    },
    {
        "question": "1000. Did you finish these tasks? Yes, I ...........",
        "options": ["did", "have", "was"],
        "correctAnswer": "did"
    }
]
